(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-30T12:34:40.898351",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Oh, minasan...
Oh, everyone...
Ugh, I don't feel so good.
Ugh...
Feel like I'm gonna collapse with sickness.
I feel like I'm gonna collapse from sickness.
Like I just went through a freaking portal
or something crazy just happened.
At least I can see chat. How are you--
Oh wait, no, I'm okay.
Don't you worry about me. I'm-- I'm fine.
There's a-- there's a lot of Deadbeats here today.
Maybe Deadbeats, KFP members, Takodachi,
there's just a lot of...
Ugh, people.
Woah, let me catch my breath for a minute here.
Hold on. Woah.
That was some crazy travelling that I just did.
I think I went through like a a wormhole or something.
I think I went through like a wormhole or something.
It's not my fault that my eyes are done.
No, hey, wait a minute.
Hey, don't you start saying... don't you start saying stuff like that,
I swear to God I'll beat you within an inch of your life.
It's fine.
We're supposed to celebrate my fifth anniversary.
I'm five!
Can you guys believe I'm five?
Hold on, I probably should adjust the camera a little bit, you can't see me, hang on.
Oh, you know what, I think I can take control of it if I click... There we go.
Hey there.
What's up?
What do you... what do you think?
Do you like it? Do you like this new outfit I found myself in?
Oh, you look cute, thank you.
Um, a lot of the girls told me I look like a robber, which, now that I've said it, you guys, you know, might might be able to see it.
Um, a lot of the girls told me I look like a robber, which, now that I've said it, you guys, you know, might be able to see it.
But, you know, there are various things that I can do and and change with this, so.
But, you know, there are various things that I can do and change with this, so.
So, the beautiful, oh thank you, you look amazing, thank you very much, nice outfit, they say.
I'm glad that you like it. There's there's many things that I can do, um...
I'm glad that you like it. There's many things that I can do, um...
...but I feel like I should, you know, a good magician never shows all of their tricks, like, right away, you know?
So, I figure we have lots of time to celebrate what is essentially five years of all of us being together, right?
So, I feel like I should be a little happier about that, right?
I thankfully I can do something about that.
Thankfully I can do something about that.
Yay! Five years! Five years!
But, you know, as as you guys know, your Mori has like a little bit of a resting b-word face, so I kind of have to force myself to smile a little bit.
But, you know, as you guys know, your Mori has like a little bit of a resting b-word face, so I kind of have to force myself to smile a little bit.
That's okay. I I can do that.
That's okay. I can do that.
I can totally do that.
Oh wait, I'm sorry, I grabbed you. I didn't mean to grab you.
What if I... pew!
Pew pew pew pew!
Hold on, I I can do more than that though, that's not I'm not a one-trick pony or anything.
Hold on, I can do more than that though, that's not I'm not a one-trick pony or anything.
This is my favorite face ever!
Cuz this is this is how I look all the time off-stream, when you don't see me, it's like I I click stream, oh waddy, and then my eyes just immediately shrink to look like this.
Cuz this is how I look all the time off-stream, when you don't see me, it's like I click stream, oh waddy, and then my eyes just immediately shrink to look like this.
Just just so you know, this is...
Just so you know, this is...
This is my usual, this is my normal, my nature.
So shocked.
Shock is one word for it, tu and ghost cat see this every day, you're right, you're right Deadbeat, this is this is the mommy that they're used to.
Shock is one word for it, tu and ghost cat see this every day, you're right, you're right Deadbeat, this is the mommy that they're used to.
And then this is just my current, my constant state of being.
You guys don't mind, right?
Resting b-word face.
No problem, no problem.
Hi.
No, you guys are you guys I'm just tired, but I'm I'm happy.
No, you guys are... I'm just tired, but I'm happy.
I'm happy, but I'm tired.
This is this is normal, this is usual.
This is normal, this is usual.
Nope, it's all good.
But but someday, um, we have plans to get like some some really good, very decent face tracking, so look forward to that.
But someday, um, we have plans to get like some really good, very decent face tracking, so look forward to that.
Um, oh by the way, just really quick before before we get too in deep into this, um, I have an announcement.
Um, oh by the way, just really quick before we get too in-depth into this, um, I have an announcement.
There's a special goody available to you guys.
You guys like goodies?
I like goodies.
Um, we have we have a very special item.
Um, we have a very special item.
For those of you that use VR Chat,
it is a penlight for this specific event that you'll be able to claim.
There's going to be a link in the description, they're updating it as we speak.
Um, and also there will be a link on Twitter, Twitter, uh, for you guys to grab it.
It's very special, it's got the logo from this specific event.
And I I wanted to put it out there, um, thankfully with the help, um, of AEV and, um, and VR Chat,
And I wanted to put it out there, um, thankfully with the help, um, of AEV and, um, and VR Chat,
uh, to do something really special for you guys.
This is a claimable item just to celebrate this this big event together with you guys.
This is a claimable item just to celebrate this big event together with you guys.
I hope you guys will enjoy it and use it in VR Chat and have lots of fun with your friends if we ever do something like future concerts
in VR Chat, I'm I'm always really open to like figuring out new tech and stuff like that, uh, together with, you know, the other members and all these really amazing technically powerful...
in VR Chat, I'm always really open to like figuring out new tech and stuff like that, uh, together with, you know, the other members and all these really amazing technically powerful...
this amazing world that we're going to go explore.
Oh man, it's nostalgic. It's nostalgic.
Um, I want to do more fun stuff like this, that is what I've realized after working so hard on this project for so long.
So, um... So, yeah.
Uh, thanks for for being a part of it though, you guys. I feel like I can get even wackier.
Uh, thanks for being a part of it though, you guys. I feel like I can get even wackier.
Hold on, expressions face face expression. Hold on, delay.
Wack!
This is an emote you get to see very often.
Uh there's also constant sleep. Is this This too is Saiyan sky, my beloved. Now I look like her.
Uh, there's also... Is this—This too is Saiyan Sky, my beloved. Now I look like her.
Um we we should move along I know that we should move along.
Um, we should move along. I know that we should move along.
Um, first I want to give a really huge thank you to two folks who made this outfit possible. Thank you so much, too.
The designer of this outfit, Nanoless.
You guys know Nanoless?
Nanoless is so amazing and just has the most beautiful designs ever, outfit designs.
Nanoless is so amazing and just has the most beautiful outfit designs ever.
And I had wanted to work with Nano for the longest time, so I'm so glad that I got this outfit fully designed by Nanoless.
Hopefully we we might get we might get like a reference image at some point.
Hopefully we might get like a reference image at some point.
But thank you so much to Nano for creating this outfit. I love it so dearly. I want to use it in music videos. Um so please look forward to to that in the future.
But thank you so much to Nano for creating this outfit. I love it so dearly. I want to use it in music videos. Um, so please look forward to that in the future.
And I also want to give a big ups to Yuli as well who designed the model for this outfit. Uh did all the 3D modeling for it.
And I also want to give a big ups to Yuli as well who designed the model for this outfit, did all the 3D modeling for it.
So Nanoless did the design and Yuli did the actual 3D modeling
and neither of those are easy tasks at all.
Um so thank you for going out of your way to make time for uh just a a little five-year-old Reaper like me.
Um, so thank you for going out of your way to make time for a little five-year-old Reaper like me.
I I say five, I'm actually known as old, but you get you get the point. It's been five years together, right?
I say five, I'm actually a lot older, but you get the point. It's been five years together, right?
Um, but yay! Yuli so so goded, Nanoless so goded. Thank you so much.
Um, but yay! Yuli is so godated, Nanoless is so goded. Thank you so much.
And of course, this world, we're going to get a little bit more in to the creation of this world as well, I think.
And of course, this world... we're going to get a little bit more into the creation of this world as well, I think.
But before we do that, we got to kind of I want to kind of explore a little bit, you know?
There's stuff to look at around here, you guys. Hold on.
Did Did you guys see Hey, hang on a second. There are a bunch of signs around here.
Did you guys see—hey, hang on a second. There are a bunch of signs around here.
My Reaper looking extra cute. Thank you. You're Your Reaper is is trying to figure out where the heck we are, but there are some clues here and there that we can look at, right?
My Reaper looking extra cute. Thank you. Your Reaper is trying to figure out where the heck we are, but there are some clues here and there that we can look at, right?
So let's take a look at this.
I can read due to a thanatological incident the elevator is out of service.
Whether you are alive or dead, please seek out your local psychopomp.
I know I know Thanatos, that's a a persona. Uh due to a thanatological I know I know that means death. It's like Latin or something like that. I don't know.
I know Thanatos, that's a persona. Due to a thanatological... I know that means death. It's like Latin or something, I don't know.
The thanatological incident, the elevator is out of service. Whether you are alive or dead, please seek out your local psychopomp. I know a couple psychopomps.
None of them are in holo, but maybe someday we'll get a psychopomp. I feel like we'd be really good friends and get along.
I don't know, five years I've been here, we haven't had a psychopomp, but who knows in the next five we could maybe welcome one.
I don't know, in the five years I've been here we haven't had a psychopomp, but who knows, in the next five we could maybe welcome one.
That will be cool. Amen elevator, see that's what I'm thinking. I remember this elevator even just from the shape of it, right?
That would be cool. Amen's elevator—see, that's what I'm thinking. I remember this elevator, even just from the shape of it, right?
Do not annoy the elevator attendant, Amen.
Yeah no, this is this is definitely this is 100% Amen's elevator, I think. What happened to it? You guys know what the heck happened to this place?
Yeah, no, this is definitely 100% Amen's elevator, I think. What happened to it? Do you guys know what the heck happened to this place?
Maximum capacity 12 people. 50 if smol. Do you guys remember when we had less than 12 people? Cuz I do.
"Maximum capacity: 12 people, 50 if smol." Do you guys remember when we had less than 12 people? Because I do.
I remember when we had less than 12. Look at that. Then not everybody would have been able to fit into the elevator.
You know, what about what about um Advent and Justice, right? They wouldn't be able to fit. I mean, if they could if they were small.
You know, what about Advent and Justice, right? They wouldn't be able to fit. I mean, they could if they were small.
the elevator would need to be renovated so that we could all fit. Amen, Amen elevator back then. Small long times, yeah. The time has flown by so fast, says chat.
The elevator would need to be renovated so that we could all fit. Amen, Amen's elevator!
Time flies when you're having fun, right guys? Let's see. Do not fall into the time vortex.
We don't know what will happen, but it doesn't look good. Okay, going to heed those wise words. Strong quantum fluctuations, keep yourself observed at all times to avoid disappearing.
Hey what the heck? I don't want to disappear I have stuff to do!
Speaking of stuff to do, maybe we should maybe we should move right along um because there are some really cool spots around here and I think I see Don't get too excited. Oh gosh, sorry. I really shook you around a little bit.
Speaking of stuff to do, maybe we should move right along... because there are some really cool spots around here, and I think I see—Don't get too excited! Oh gosh, sorry, I really shook you around a little bit.
Get this, Deadbeats.
A resort.
Will Mori Calliope be going there? Probably, probably—yes. I will for the sake of...
Will Mori Calliope be going there?
Probably... yes. I will for the sake of...
For the sake of this journey, we'll go to the resort.
For the sake of this journey,
we'll go to the resort.
You guys want to come with? Though, I don't want to go alone, so my deadbeats gotta come with me, okay?
You guys want to come with?
I don't want to go alone, so my deadbeats gotta come with me, okay?
You guys gotta come with me. Is that right?
You guys gotta come with me.
Is that right?
You guys cool with that?
Hey.
I could kind of use a rest.
It would be nice.
We got some fun surprises today. Uh so please look forward to them.
We got some fun surprises today,
so please look forward to them.
But I guess we'll try and make our way out of here then, shall we?
I guess we'll try and make our way
out of here then, shall we?
Mm.
Let's do it.
We need to observe you to prevent a disappearance.
We need to observe you
to prevent a disappearance.
You make a good point, Skeletons. You make a good point.
You make a good point, Skeletons.
You make a good point.
Well, let's go ahead and head on over then. Shall we?
Well, let's go ahead and head on over
then, shall we?
What does this say?
Hub?
Oh, I can't s—
Sorry, chat's kind of in my what. That's all right.
Sorry, chat's kind of in my way.
That's all right.
I I want you guys here. I want you I want you here, I want you here, so...
I want you guys here.
I want you here, so...
It's no problem. Hub area, it says.
Okay, observing...
They're observing right now.
Okay. Monetans, do you hear that?
They're observing. Also Monetans are here today working as hard as possible with cameras and such. Thank you, Monetans.
They're observing. Also Monetans are here
working hard today with cameras and such.
All right, well, I guess off we go to the resort.
All right, well, I guess off we go
to the resort.
Oh gosh.
I don't like going to resorts because the deadbeats I feel like I'm going to give in to my my base, you know, human instincts instead of my my Reaper side, which says work, work, work.
I don't like going to resorts because
I feel like I'm going to give in to my base
human instincts instead of my Reaper side...
My human side says it's time for vacation.
...which says work, work, work.
So let's let's just go.
So let's just go.
Let's just go and see what happens, you know?
Making my way uptown.
Whoa.
I really need to fix my posture.
No, it's it's fine.
No, it's fine.
It's fine. It's fine. My posture is not the best.
It's fine. My posture is not the best.
Also I can walk on water, by the way, in case in case you didn't know.
Also, I can walk on water, by the way,
in case you didn't know.
You guys like my Naruto run?
It's just my my current state of being and and movement. You're back!
It's just my current state of being
and movement. You're back!
Oh wait, did you guys see the design on my back, the skull? That's my logo.
Oh wait, did you guys see the design
on my back? The skull? That's my logo.
That's my logo. I really want to release this jacket someday.
That's my logo.
I really want to release this jacket someday.
Would not be cool? It'd be pretty cool jacket to release as merch.
Would that not be cool?
It'd be a pretty cool jacket as merch.
I feel like I released too many clothing items though.
I feel like I released too many
clothing items, though.
We really don't need that many.
Well, anyway, I guess we better better get out of here. Uh What am I looking at? Oh gosh, I don't want to show you guys what the clothes can do yet.
Well, anyway, I guess we better
get out of here.
What am I looking at?
We'll get to that later, shall we?
Okay.
Let us be on our way up the stairs. I'll try to My posture's great.
Let us be on our way up the stairs.
I'll try to—my posture's great.
I never would bend my back while I walk. That's not something that Mori Calliope would ever do.
I never would bend my back while I walk.
That's not something Mori Calliope would do.
Whoa!
Do you guys see this?
This is a full-on this is a full-blown What's Oh.
This is a full-on...
This is a full-blown... What's—oh.
Hold on a second.
Hey, what's this little switch here? It's got a camera. Can I activate it, I wonder? Oh.
Hey, what's this little switch here?
It's got a camera. Can I activate it?
Whoa! Check it.
You guys get a sweeping view.
Nice perspective.
Anything wrong with your spine? No, it needs relaxation, which is why we've come here to this resort.
Anything wrong with your spine?
No, it needs relaxation, which is why we're here.
It looks like I could run around it as like a Dark Souls map.
It looks like I could run around it,
like a Dark Souls map.
Not everything is Dark Souls so just you know.
Not everything is Dark Souls,
so just you know.
There's a bar!
Wait, hold on. I just barely missed. Hang on, I have to fix my knee.
Wait, hold on. I just barely missed.
Hang on, I have to fix my knee.
There's a bar, Deadbeats!
Hold on, we're in trouble now.
Hang on, let's get to the center here. Whoa!
Hang on, let's get to the center here.
Whoa!
I don't look very enthused, but I am excited.
I don't look very enthused,
but I am excited.
No, wait a minute, Deadbeat. Wait, it's not time yet. It's not time.
No, wait a minute, deadbeats.
Wait, it's not time yet.
It's not time. We have to bar Mori.
It's not time.
We have to... Bar Mori.
Do you guys remember Bar Mori? Cuz I remember Bar Mori.
Do you guys remember Bar Mori?
Cuz I remember Bar Mori.
Oh, that was so fun.
I loved Bar Mori. We should have had more adventures there, but that's on me.
I loved Bar Mori. We should've had
more adventures there, but that's on me.
That's on me. I got into busy with other stuff. My knee's been feeling tired these days.
That's on me. I got too busy
with other stuff. My knee's been tired.
There we go.
Fancy, classic.
This is not VR chat, this is a vlog on Calli's vacation.
This is not VRChat.
This is a vlog on Calli's vacation.
Wait, no, you got it all wrong! You I'm I'm working hard, I promise.
Wait, no, you got it all wrong!
I'm working hard, I promise.
Look at the way that the the water reflects off of me though.
Look at the way the water
reflects off of me, though.
Innit pretty neat?
Hold on, can I do peace?
Peace...
Peace. I'm doing a pose. I'm doing a peace.
Peace.
I'm doing a pose. I'm doing peace.
Hope you guys get lots of screenshots.
And remember to use #5YearsOfMori to share your favorite screenshots, okay?
And remember to use #5YearsOfMori
to share your favorite screenshots, okay?
#5YearsOfMori. You can also share your favorite memories...
#5YearsOfMori. You can also share
your favorite memories...
... or, you know, fan art too, if you want. Like whatever whatever you want to use.
...or, you know, fan art too, if you want.
Like whatever you want to use.
#5YearsOfMori to celebrate five years of the Grim Reaper invading your personal space.
#5YearsOfMori to celebrate five years
of the Grim Reaper invading your space.
And by personal I mean like your home, you know, cuz when you watch me, I'm there in your home.
And by personal, I mean like your home.
Cuz when you watch me, I'm right there.
Well, I guess we should look around maybe a little bit more.
Well, I guess we should look around
maybe a little bit more.
Cool. Whoa, what's this?
I dare not,
I dare not lay down.
We don't have time for that. We don't have time.
Let's let's get moving around a little bit 'cause we got stuff to do.
Hang on a sec. Woah, woah, woah!
Yago?
Hey, there's a bar over there though.
There's a there's a bar. Before we get to Yago,
can we just can we hit the bar really quick?
Hang on.
No, this is this is big. This is big, big news.
All right.
Deadbeats.
Welcome to Bar Mori.
Welcome to Bar Mori— oh, you guys are back here.
I wonder if I can — let me get a martini, wait.
Hang on, I'm I'm pulling you over here. I'm pulling my chat in front of my face so that I can I can see them. Okay.
Pop, float, and we're okay, there we go.
Now I can see you perfectly!
Now I can I can take your order. What would you guys like?
Can I get some whiskey?
Yes, I actually I saved some just for this special occasion, so, uh, let me go grab it.
Right here. Yes.
Welcome to Bar Mori. Here it is.
Hold hold to grab— oh, this one.
Hold to grab. Oh, this.
Okay, I got it.
No, I— ah!
Wait, I dropped it! Okay, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
I'm not very good at this.
Maybe I really do need a vacation.
Wait, no. Okay, hang on. The melon soda, see that's a that's a good choice.
All right, here's— got any glasses here?
We don't— um, well, all right, all right, chat, this is for you.
Fetch!
It landed perfectly upright!
It landed perfectly.
You know what, this reminds me, I used to tell you guys about my my old job.
I used to have a tough old job that I did back in the day and I I served somebody like a a drink that didn't have enough like vodka or tequila in it and they threw it in my face.
I remember telling you guys about that.
Well, I've been through a lot and I'm ready to unleash my rage!
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Something happened.
Okay. Sorry, I had a blackout right there for a second.
All right, is this amaretto?
Can I juggle it?
Yeah, I can.
Oh man, she's too good.
Oh, she's too skilled.
Oh god, I dropped it!
Okay, it's 'cause I got cocky. That happens all the time for me.
Uh, hang on, I got it.
No problem.
So talented, they say.
Big ups!
What do you mean? No, no, there's no EN curse!
Stop, Chigauyo!
It's coming out of your paycheck. You know what, I think about that—
Uh!
I may have thrown it too far.
Oh, there it goes!
Hey, this is way this is better than I thought.
Whoa, this is this is actually very stress relieving.
Believe it or not.
And sometimes you just feel like you gotta
I was supposed to be serving the deadbeats. Is this the thanks that they get after 5 years of being loyal supporters of the Grim Reaper?
You know what? Yeah, it is.
It's messed up. I have other goodies.
I have other— I have other goodies for you guys, I promise.
Yes, yes, it is. It's so worth it. You guys are too kind to me.
Deadbeats are the kindest. What the heck?
Waffle House? What you got? What you got?
There's no—
Forget your street fights.
This a trench war.
Hang on.
Can I pick up the—
[Gasp]
Oh man, I can pick up everything!
They freaking killed it with this. Who is they? I will tell you shortly.
But anyway, we we could play with—
I could throw bottles at you guys all day,
but we do have to move right along because we got a schedule to keep!
A schedule to keep!
All right, let's go check out
what the heck happened over here.
Um,
what am I looking at?
That's uh
That's real special.
Right over there, the Yago, let me see if I can pull you guys up before me again. Get in front of my face.
But yeah, so you can see— hang on, I got you.
Now don't be afraid.
Don't be afraid, my small lambs. This man will not hurt you. He's just— He just has really expensive shorts.
That's uh that's my boss, by the way. This is Michelangelo's Yago.
Golden swim trunks, actually uh 24 karat gold swim trunks on my boss. Good for him, good for him.
Thank you for thank you for the resort resources.
Hey, is that Justice?
Cool! We also have paintings of my cute kohai as well here.
Very nice.
And then the architecture— Whoa, okay!
We're not that ancient.
Yo, who made this?
Who made this mit—
I don't know. What do you guys think?
Ancient myth.
Oh man. This is where my membership money goes, that Deadbeats right? It sure is.
Right here, to a grand carving such as this.
Myth, yes, the the oldest and most decrepit and most ancient.
Myth, yes... the oldest, most decrepit, and most ancient.
After that we moved into the the Promise age.
After that, we moved into the Promise age.
I promise, cute.
I love that this one is different and that it looks like it could be a kindergartener's drawing,
I love that this one is different and that it looks like a kindergartener's drawing,
but it's clearly not. Like they made it with intent, so it's not it's not really what it is, but
but it's clearly not. Like they made it with intent, so it's not...
Let's go Promise!
And then we also have, oh we can't forget them,
And then we also have—oh, we can't forget them—
ad uh Advent right here. There's Advent.
Advent right here. There's Advent.
Look at all my cute kouhai.
Solidified in history.
What a place of beautiful art. There's a lot of artisticness that went into this.
A lot of artistry.
Oh man, we got to we got to give thanks though to whoever put all of this together, right?
Oh man, we gotta give thanks though to whoever put all of this together, right?
Shall we go take a quick look?
Here we go.
This map was created by SEAFOAMBOY (@SEAFOAMBOI) MAP DESIGN AND CONCEPT, ART AND MODELLING
This map was created by SeafoamBoy—map design and concept, art and modelling.
And then MMAELLON (@MMAEALLON) PROGRAMMING AND CAMERA SYSTEMS
And then Mmaellon—programming and camera systems.
Wow, why why are we why are we looking at this plaque like they're dead or something? Did they die?
Wow, why are we looking at this plaque like they're dead or something? Did they die?
I don't I don't think that they died or anything like that.
I don't think that they died or anything like that.
They did so well though. I mean, Seafoam's Seafoam's vision here is just so amazing.
They did so well though. I mean, Seafoam's vision here is just so amazing.
I can see there's so much nostalgia and love for the five years that HoloEN has been together like this.
I just I think it's such a cool concept, and I'm so excited to share all of this with you guys. It's so, so cool,
I just think it's such a cool concept, and I'm so excited to share all of this with you guys. It's so, so cool,
probably the one of the coolest things I've ever done in those five years is get a place like this
probably one of the coolest things I've ever done in those five years is get a place like this...
get to visit a place like this, right?
And then of course we can't forget Maellon, who has helped so much with the programming and the camera systems.
I mean the camera systems my favorite part of this whole thing, like normally you can't
I mean, the camera systems are my favorite part of this whole thing, like normally you can't
do all this crazy stuff with cameras, but I'm so, so, so grateful.
Ah, thank you so much to you guys for the help and all the programming too.
Man, my I my brain is you guys know how my brain is, it's it's not capable of of handling uh things that programmer brain can handle,
Man, my brain is—you guys know how my brain is—it's not capable of handling things that a programmer brain can handle,
so I really I really appreciate it.
Um, and I'm so excited! I don't look like I'm excited, but I'm excited to to get to the rest of it.
Um, and I'm so excited—I don't look like I'm excited, but I'm excited to get to the rest of it.
So yay! We know—
hey, hold on a second.
Well, that's okay. I invited that conversation, so
But there's something I want to... there's something that's been bugging me, Deadbeats, while we've been here.
Um... It's that I feel like I did something here already. I feel like I have a memory of being here at a different time.
And I'm not just talking about the fact that it reminds me of the original Myth lobby in many ways, but oh wow, I really did just drop drinks everywhere, huh?
Okay. Um, that's kind of messed up.
I really shouldn't have done that. That was very rude of me.
I feel as though I've I've sung a song here before with friends.
I feel as though I've sung a song here before with friends.
Um... and I want... I'm thinking I might end up remembering that.
I think I sung a couple of songs here, and so I think I want to
flash back to those if I can. I feel like if I channel like my inner my inner most mind, my inner brain,
flashback to those if I can. I feel like if I channel like my inner most mind, my inner brain,
then I can have like a that's a Raven moment where like you gaze into the future, but instead it's the past
then I can have like a "That's So Raven" moment where like you gaze into the future, but instead it's the past!
Things left will be a breeze
Sorry, sorry. Um, anyway, so let's let's do that, everybody. Let's
Let's go! Flashback!
暗くなる頃始まるパーティ 集める人種は魑魅魍魎
A party starts as it gets dark; the crowd gathers—demons and monsters.
明日なき夜にダークな遊び that's my design さあ創造
Dark play in a night with no tomorrow, that's my design, now creation.
刺激が欲しい命の限り 迷えるアタシと夜通しイイ？
Wanting stimulation for all I'm worth, through the night with lost me, is that okay?
あらあらあらあら ホントはずっともう oh oh 楽しいフリして aay aay
Ara ara ara, truth is it's been long oh oh, pretending to have fun aay aay.
消えたアタシを oh oh キミが見つけてねほら
The disappeared me oh oh, you found me, look.
フラフラするでしょう クラクラ来るでしょう
You'll feel dizzy, right? You'll feel dizzy, right?
ホロホロとろけそう そうでしょう flash bang
Melting away, right? Flash bang!
フラフラするでしょう クラクラ来るでしょう
You'll feel dizzy, right? You'll feel dizzy, right?
そろそろ壊れそう そうでしょう flash bang
Breaking down soon, right? Flash bang!
まどろむunderground 浮かれた開放感
Dozing underground, a dizzying sense of liberation.
剥がれたペルソナ 放り投げ break it down
Stripped-off persona, throw it away, break it down.
だんだん崩れてく感覚 染まるのは息吸うようにカンタン
Feeling like it's crumbling bit by bit, stained as naturally as breathing.
変わりゆくアタシ 時は待ちなし 涙を濁りし あらあらあらあらあら
Changing me, time waits for no one, muddying tears, ara ara ara ara!
いやぁなんか転生した？ uh みたいなお異世界感纏って 違う人みたいだな
Wait, did I reincarnate? Like an alternate-world vibe, like a different person.
そりゃあ今日もオ美しい 出会って思ったんだよ you choose me
Of course you're beautiful today too, meeting you made me think, you choose me.
だけどあの頃の君はもう モボロシの様に フッとなくなりそう
But back then you were already like a phantom, about to vanish away.
それがフラッシュしてバックすんだ 目が回るんだ グルグルグルグル
Flashing back, head spinning around and around, round and round.
ホントはずっともう oh oh 戻れないね aay aay
Truth is it's been long oh oh, can't go back aay aay.
ちらつく心 oh oh キミが探してよほら
Flickering heart oh oh, you go look for it, look.
フラフラするでしょう クラクラ来るでしょう
You'll feel dizzy, right? You'll feel dizzy, right?
ホロホロとろけそう そうでしょう flash bang
Melting away, right? Flash bang!
暗くなる頃始まるパーティ 集める人種は魑魅魍魎
The party begins when it becomes dark, the gathering of people is wicked.
明日なき夜にダークな遊び that's my design さあ創造
Dark play in a night without tomorrow. That's my design, now creation.
刺激が欲しい命の限り
I want stimulation as long as life lasts.
迷えるアタシと夜通しイイ？あらいららいらら
Are you going through the night with me, wandering? Oh dear!
ホントはずっともう oh oh 楽しいフリして aay aay
Honestly, I've been pretending to be happy for a long time.
消えたアタシを oh oh キミが見つけてねほら
You find the me who disappeared, look.
フラフラするでしょう クラクラ来るでしょう
It will make you dizzy, it will come to make you faint.
ホロホロとろけそうそうでしょう flash bang
It looks like it's going to melt, doesn't it? Flash bang.
フラフラするでしょう クラクラ来るでしょう
It will make you dizzy, it will come to make you faint.
そろそろ壊れそうそうでしょう flash bang
It looks like it's about to break soon, doesn't it? Flash bang.
まどろむ under ground 浮遊した解放感
A submerged open feeling, I throw away...
剥がれたペルソナ放り投げ break it down
...the peeled-off persona, break it down.
だんだん崩れてく感覚染まるのは息吸う様にカンタン
The sensation of crumbling gradually, easy like breathing.
変わっていくアタシ時は待ったなし涙を渇しあらいららいらら
I'm changing, time waits for no one, draining tears, oh dear!
いやいままなんか転生した？みたいない異世界感纏って違う人みたいだ
Huh, did I reincarnate? Feeling like a different world, wearing it like a different person.
そりゃあ今日も美おもい出会って思ったんだ you choose me
You're beautiful today too, I thought when I met you, you choose me.
だけどあの頃の君はもうモナロシの様にフッとなくなそう
But the you of that time is about to disappear like a phantom.
みたいな異世界感 纏って違う人みたいだ
Wearing a different world feeling, like a different person.
そりゃあ今日も美しく 出会ったと思ったんだ you choose me
You're beautiful today too, I thought when I met you, you choose me.
身体あの頃のキミはもう
Your body from back then...
それがフラッシュしてバックすんだ目が回るんだ
It flashes and backs up, my eyes are spinning, round and round.
ぐるぐるぐるぐる
Round and round.
ホントはきっともう oh oh
Honestly, I'm sure I can't go back anymore, oh oh.
戻れないよねええ
Can't go back anymore.
ちらつく心 oh oh キミが探しで
Watch out for the flickering heart, you find me...
キミが探しで
You are searching for...
ほら フラフラするでしょう
Look, it will make you dizzy.
クラクラ来るでしょう
It will come to make you faint.
ホロホロとろけそうそうでしょう flash bang
It looks like it's going to melt, doesn't it? Flash bang.
フラッシュ バン！
Flash bang!
ギラギラ今宵の show さあさあ踊りましょう
Dazzling show tonight, let's dance.
真っ白く目眩むほどほら焼き付けてよ flash bang
Burning it into my eyes until blinding white, flash bang.
フラッシュ バン
Flash bang.
Nice job, ChadCast!
But, but, but, but... well done, you guys got some moves!
Oh god. What's she doing? What's she doing?
Are you good? I was thinking you could use a little rest.
Iris, I think I think you guys need to go relax.
IRyS, I think you guys need to go relax.
You guys need to go take a break.
Have some fun at the resort, you know, there's a cool bar over there, there's a other statue.
Have some fun at the resort, you know, there's a cool bar over there, there's another statue.
Yeah, run! Go run! Bye you two!
Oh god, I have a feeling it's about to get real wild back there. Maybe we should do another song though in the meantime, huh?
Bye guys, they're gone.
Don't have fun, don't worry about them.
Don't worry about them.
Let's... let's do another song, shall we? Let's go!
Let's um... let's do another song, shall we? Let's go!
My camouflage
What'cha gonna do? Shit, take a walk!
"Play the role of 'bad girl'" like I had a choice
I could be your "seiso - should - you - say - so" hush my voice
Double take, go figure! A disappearing act
Secret sinners, so you rang? Can't fool me like tick-tick bang.
カモフラ there you go
Camouflage there you go
(秘)な逃避行
Secret getaway
どこまでも匿名希望
Anonymous request wherever I go
Excuse to see some proof it's me
Flip all that, don't react, eyes right here
So crazy, what'cha on?
Predicting all my flaws, but all you're seeing is my camouflage
Whoah-overload! Hey dead beat, why so shocked?
Your mona lisa talks. Still ain't nothing new, shit, can't y'all knock?
My camouflage (Ain't it something?)
My camouflage (Ain't i something?)
My camouflage
What'cha gonna do? Shit, take a walk!
Come alive, cuz I shift with the scene and vibe
And I dip, shuffle, lean with the moment
Steal a glance, stop, no chance, "This who you gotta be"
カモフラ where you go
Camouflage where you go
壁側の向こう
Beyond the wall
すり抜けるこの包囲網
Slipping through this siege net
Excuse to see some proof it's me. Flip all that, don't react, eyes right here
So crazy, what'cha on? Predicting all my flaws
But all you're seeing is my camouflage
Whoah-overload! Hey dead beat, why so shocked? Your mona lisa talks. Still ain't nothing new, shit, can't y'all knock?
my camouflage
what’cha gonna do? shit, take a walk!
what'cha gonna do? shit, take a walk!
my camouflage
what’cha gonna do? shit, take a walk!
what'cha gonna do? shit, take a walk!
play the role of bad girl
like i had a choice
i could be your "seiso-should-you-say-so" hush my voice
double take, go figure!
a disappearing act
secret sinners, so you rang?
can’t fool me like tick-tick bang
can't fool me like tick-tick bang
kamofura there you go
(secret) na touhikou
doko made mo tokumei kibou
excuse to see
some proof it’s me
some proof it's me
flip all that, don’t react
flip all that, don't react
eyes right here
whoah-oh!
so crazy, what ‘chu on?
so crazy, what 'chu on?
predicting all my flaws
but all you’re seeing is my camouflage
but all you're seeing is my camouflage
whoah-overload!
hey dead beat, why so shocked?
your mona lisa talks
still ain’t nothing new, shit, can’t y’all knock?
still ain't nothing new, shit, can't y'all knock?
my camouflage
what’cha gonna do? shit, take a walk!
what'cha gonna do? shit, take a walk!
my camouflage
what’cha gonna do? shit, take a walk!
what'cha gonna do? shit, take a walk!
my camouflage
what’cha gonna do? shit, take a walk!
what'cha gonna do? shit, take a walk!
my camouflage
what’cha gonna do? shit, take a walk!
what'cha gonna do? shit, take a walk!
guess i gotta use this camouflage
Oh, wow...
Thank you, thank you, you guys for dancing with me today!
Wow, and you guys sound so good, too!
You, you're really there, oh my gosh!
Ah, I'm being hugged!
I'm being hugged!
Oh my gosh, ah!
Wait, go enjoy the resort, you guys!
Have fun!
But get some rest! Bye-bye!
There are doggie treats over there,
maybe.
Go find 'em! Go find 'em!
Ah, maybe, maybe I should relax here for a little bit.
No!
We have more songs to do, dead beats!
No rest for the wicked!
So while my friends are enjoying the resort, I'm gonna go do some more work.
Just for a little bit, though.
We'll come back later, right?
Yeah, that's what I'm gonna do.
Well, let's get out of here.
No, no, we can come back later.
We can come back later.
I'm out. I'm auskeys.
I'm out.
Yeah, don't, don't worry, don't worry about those guys.
Hey, listen, in fairness, don't worry about the Xbox mic either.
I did that to them on purpose.
It was not them, it was me. I cursed their mics with Xbox mic syndrome because...
Choking on my own spit.
Because, because their voices are too cute, and they needed to be nerfed. That's all that it was.
But no, it's not, it's not their fault.
You sure? It was all me.
How dare you! That's fine.
I will take I will take your insults. I will take all of them.
Also, if my friends, if my friends ever need me to come in for a song and like tank all the bad words, let me know.
I'll do it.
I went through, I went through a period in the past five years where I was like, here, we can walk and talk, we can walk and talk.
I went through a period of time within the past five years being like, you know what, maybe I should calm down with the curse words.
But, but it's just because, you know, I'm getting to be an old woman, right?
As you can see, I'm walking like a decrepit, crotchety old lady with my shoulders all the way down.
Uh, but honestly, if it's for a song,
who cares, right?
It's just just for the F-word.
Yeah, speed walking, get old curse words. We stay family-friendly here.
But, to be honest, to be honest, I've I've heard children use fouler language than I've ever used in my life.
So, you know what, it is what it is. It is what it is. It looks like I'm rapidly roller-skating.
Maybe that's what I'm doing, maybe there are skates on the bottom of these shoes, and you guys don't even know.
Anyway, um, I look like less of a robber, don't you think, without the beanie?
I look a little bit less like I'm going to break into your home,
which is I don't know, a plus or minus depending upon how you view it.
But I can take my headphones off, too. See, there, they're gone.
They're gone.
I don't really know.
I mean, it kind of covers my jewelry, so it's kind of nice that you can see the finer details, right?
So, I've got like a little skull lapel jacket, a lapel? Maybe it's just a pin.
I don't know, but I'm really into chokers these days and spikes and stuff like that. So, yeah.
Law-abiding Reaper, oh, but of course,
but of course.
Definitely. Looking respectful.
Oh, of course, yeah. Looking checking respect.
Yeah, only with respect. With respect.
What do you guys think? Do you like the inside of my jacket, too?
It's got kind of like a checker pattern. Anyway, we're supposed to be moving...
right along, but I'm kind of taking my time around here as well.
We do have many more memories to to re-familiarize ourselves with, so
We do have many more memories to re-familiarize ourselves with, so
let me let me grab you.
let me grab you.
Oh, don't worry, you won't feel it and it won't hurt.
Okay, I've grabbed you successfully.
Let me hold on, swirl eyes? What do those look like? Hang on.
Oh, I'm still in desktop. Okay.
Swirl-eyed.
She's a little quirky and crazy. But it makes me like her more, I guess. I don't know.
You're still here after 5 years, you certainly got some taste.
If you're still here after 5 years, you certainly got some taste.
All right, let's go ahead and move. I love the architecture in this place, lots of respect to the underworldian culture here.
with our underworldian maidens.
I don't know who this lady is. Could this be the real Calliope?
Could it be the real Muse Calliope?
It could be. If it isn't, then that's now my head canon, but
But I probably should change my eyes to not be so swirly. Sorry about that, I'm just being extra quirky today.
I probably should change my eyes to not be so swirly. Sorry about that, I'm just being extra quirky today.
Lord whoopst, I'm telling you, I think that it's the original Calliope, but we're going to move with respect right behind her.
Lord, oops! I'm telling you, I think that it's the original Calliope, but we're going to move with respect right behind her.
And I wanted to say I saw this before, but I didn't want to get too ahead of myself.
Check this out, guys, where are we?
What is this place? You can see the sky and the fragments, but then beyond there's like a swirling deserted city, and then I see that there's like... I'm really interested in the hell temple that's over here.
You guys see that hell temple? I think we should go there next.
It reminds me of something that I've seen before on multiple levels, right?
I think that you guys might be able to draw the links between the places that we're visiting today and also some VR shenanigans that we've gotten down to in the past, right?
But but for now it looks cool, yay!
But for now... it looks cool, yay!
Design is wild, right? Isn't it awesome?
We're going home onto the next stage indeed, that beats indeed, like from J-Rap and G-Cook.
We're going home onto the next stage, indeed! Dead Beats indeed, like from J-Rap and G-Cook.
J-Rap and G-Cook was was my concert, right? But G-Cook 6 is my EP. Maybe it's not the best idea to use the same the same word
J-Rap and G-Cook was my concert, right? But G-Cook 6 is my EP. Maybe it's not the best idea to use the same word
in my concert slash shows because people might get confused. Anyway, we're going over the bridge
in my concert/shows because people might get confused. Anyway, we're going over the bridge
to check out what the heck this place is. I love lanterns.
So the aesthetic is pretty much on point for what I enjoy, but uh...
So the aesthetic is pretty much on point for what I enjoy, but...
Hold on, I'm getting that weird feeling again like I've been here before.
Uh hang on a sec. Hey hey hold up. You see that? It's one of those one of those camera signs.
Hang on a sec. Hey, hold up. You see that? It's one of those camera signs.
What if we touch it? Hold on a sec.
Let me see that camera camera right here. Uh this should give us sweep in view.
Let me see that camera right here. This should give us sweep-in view.
Okay, check it out.
Oh, whoa!
Okay, now I'm feeling ultra nostalgic.
I feel like this isn't the first time that I entered this place though.
Like I've I've seen it before. Uh I think I feel a memory coming on, you guys.
Like I've seen it before. I think I feel a memory coming on, you guys.
A memory singing a song with someone here.
Well, if that's the case, then let's let's check it out.
Well, if that's the case, then let's check it out.
Oh, this place is pretty cool too! Heh, there's cool stuff everywhere!
Especially, wow, this is awesome, it's got lanterns! What the heck, didn't I dance in front of that fire during G-Cook 6?
Hey, is that the pirate from the Future Island stage that was in the G-Cook 6 concert? It has to... This place is awesome. This is so cool. What the heck?
I wonder, are there any friends around here too? What friends are here, I wonder?
Are you okay? Oh, she's climbing up those stairs.
I know there's a lot of stairs. Timotine, are you okay?
I know there's a lot of... She's really wheezing. Oh god, are you okay, little one?
This place is flames. Hey there! You're so cute.
I know you can't run all this, but I can see a lot of things from down here. I I know you can. I I figured as much.
I know you can't run all this, but I can see a lot of things from down here. I know you can. I figured as much.
Whoa, hey, don't look too long though. Don't look too... Whoa, there! Whoa, she's a little close.
You got such a big head here. I didn't expect to see you like this. Oh my lord! Ugh!
No, no, I have no problem with it, just
that, really, what is it? The hogeh really sticks,
oh my god, ouch! Ouch!
Why are you beating on me? Hey! Oi, oi, always on my head!
Stop, stop it!
Why are you so crazy?
That's okay, I know the answer.
I know the answer.
I love you so much, though.
I love you more, Calli! Yeah, I can't wait to do so many things with you.
I want to do some things with you too, but one of those things is... thing!
One, one thing on this stage, in front of this fire.
Number two.
Dance on this stage in front of this fire.
Okay, what's the third one, though?
Um, be beside you.
So let's start with kissing me?
Uh, maybe late, we can not- not in front of the people.
Uh, depends on where, though. You may kiss my hand, if you want.
Okay, yeah, that's- I want that.
Perfect, perfect. All right, that's great. Show- show me sing a little, a little song—
oh god, I'm flustered now.
All right, let's- let's sing a dang song together.
How about it?
All right, play music!
Shit, one, two. Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Mori Calliope!
Reol! Let's go! Woah!
Are you listening under, one by one, to play the toy soldiers of incorporation?
Sōdō nante wa one-on-one atashi dake no ikenai sōzōgeki
Say, yatte yarimashō! I do whatever it takes now. Let the karma rain down.
I can play the hero if it means I'll be the last clown living in the twisted diorama that is industry fail
and we're in the streets where big eels those are konna mon ja nai jinsei
Sotta tte yarimashō! I do whatever it takes now. Let the karma rain down.
Mirror, mirror, tell me again, if there was stated that I'm made on a stroke?
Louder, clearer, just say it I'm enough, do you like so well?
Hige kake te tori kō! Each gig gets dead only go!
Hate to be the one to break the fairytale apart, let the cash out-dazzle misers, what if they were smart?
Chapped up, nobody cries. Step now and fall behind every idle beauty's got a fist inside of mine.
Hayachū makase, tozasu owaru magajin, o-toshizu saber datta n' ja nai?
Readin' like a ransom letter, full of stains will never clean or wash away.
Kookier this net's neck is and sonna mon ja nai jinsei
Sōchaku-teki mō kōkai, hane-baki mukashi mizo-zume chiisaku jienai shōbibu
Boku-boku de wa naku natta koku ga kaku yajima o itsumo anzen kakeru taku
Saki ni moto shō-in kara no way out sugide sōdō nagasemo shittari no way out
Kimi ne! Color it in, I got you, katchō-katchō nananin'i dake no kyohaku takanami wa chō-sō-sō!
Sō-sō saru dashi wa, sore de ii ka? Ne, mirā, mirā, odoroke!
Mirror, mirror, tell me again, if there was stated that I'm made on a stroke?
Louder, clearer, just say it I'm enough, do you like so well?
Hige kake te tori kō! Each gig gets dead only go!
Hayabusa-ke no zentō, o-toshizu kattoku.
Hate to be the one to break the fairytale apart, let the cash out-dazzle misers, what if they were smart?
Chapped up, nobody cries. Step now and fall behind every idle beauty's got a fist inside of mine.
Kamerusuto follow the irrelevant, you only gotta celibate, you only gotta get out of your celibate, and if you ever make it better hope that you can take it with you.
So as good as make it, it's a live or a crust to break.
I don't care anymore! Mirror, mirror, tell me again, if there was stated that I'm made on a stroke?
Louder, clearer, just say it I'm enough, do you like so well?
I'm freaking out! I'm freaking out!
It's just business, man!
Mirror, mirror, tell me again, if there was stated that I'm made on a stroke?
Louder, clearer, just say it I'm enough, do you like so well?
Each gig gets dead only go!
Paradise or hell, I might be tasting our hate, I'll be loving living in ice and coal.
Let the record spin on like a carousel! Oh my god, it's a mad-mad world.
It's a paradise when you've got me tight. Walk on the monochrome set, no more shiyou.
Hakunai sonomama no zetsubatsu.
I heard that Gigi was freaking it, do you guys?
She was freaking it!
I think it's super cute that I feel I get the feeling that only she has chosen to be in that form.
Only G- only Gigi wanted to be so so small and rotund and cute.
Anyway, I guess we should look around a little she does that all the time. I see some gems in here. You know what's up, honey?
Gigi, Gigi, Gigi so special. Oh, I love I love her very much. She's always so nice and fun to hang out with.
I was so glad that I could I could sing on a stage like this with her. Speaking of the stage, should we look around a little bit?
Here, follow me.
What's this? This seems like a really cool view over here. I love that the lanterns have like this myth
myth uh logo on them.
Check it.
You guys see? Look, and they glow in like red and yellow
and and you can see so many different areas just from here.
Myth forever, right guys?
See that place over there, that is that Atlantis?
I want to go to Atlantis. Wait, we can't we can't get ahead of ourselves though. There are a lot of different places to look at, but
Oh man, I guess we can we can look at a little bit more of this area. Uh
Uh, let's see.
As I mentioned before in the memory, that that pirate, is that the pirate from the from uh the Future Island performance from Gigo 6?
The concert? I think it is. Look at that big guy.
And it says I think that's the kanji for king on his head.
Oh gosh, there's fire in my eyes.
We don't want to fall down there, but if we did fall down there, something cool might happen.
Maybe there's a secret underneath that fire. I want to discover the secrets.
Well, there'll be time to look at secrets later, I think.
I'm getting really getting really hot, deadbeats.
Uh, that don't feel so good.
But the heat is reminding me of something. The heat is reminding me that I think that
this wasn't the only performance that I did here.
I think there was another one with two with two other people.
If I stand here, I might be able to remember. All right, I think I do.
Okay, check it out!
players down in hell all want it the same
flawless and cautious, oh what a heckin' shame
清らかなdeathちゃん knows your sick game
Pure Death-chan knows your sick game.
(mori)
shake it
i'm a walking disaster
not half-cocked like the last girl
ya say stop, i go faster
talkin' slaughter and laughter
boom-boom bang
act a fool, i'm a misfit
a "too cool" nihilist chick
think i wanna blow up this niche
arrogant and loud, i might hit her like a light switch
pow, i'm such a cosmic pain
魅惑の痛み shut up, i ain't no hero (hero)
Seductive pain, shut up, I ain't no hero (Hero)!
サバイバルできんの？ (killすの？)
Can you survive? (Kill?)
hey, got devils in my brain
can't make 'em shut up
next, you'll say you're fed up
nah, this is what i led ya to
forget "sport"
this is war
what ya waiting for?
good lord
mori's bored
welcome to the killing floor!
got no will to run
don't look at me like i'm dumb
doomers swear "life ain't fair"
i don't care!
the end is nigh end is nigh
didn't get the memo yet? end is nigh
end is nigh
boys, line up single file
wanna end the world in style
get on some armageddon stuff like
gotta kill 'em allから end is nigh
players down in hell all want it the same
flawless and cautious, oh what a-
get a grip, red does not mean "go"
死not your 怨
Death not your 怨,
死 on the new world order's throne does that make you see the?
Death on the new world order's throne, does that make you see the?
brace for the apocalypse, they hate my guts so read my lips
don't take the bait, stick to the script
play 'em like a fool when they numbers dip
say what now? make 'em shut down
yeah, shinigami gang in a rough town
break new ground black and blue sound
まだまだぶちかましたい next round!
ah, what's on your mind? don't want to die?
price is a little big of ego
cynics wanna sit in these robes
empress got hella new clothes!
forget "sport"
this is war
what ya waiting for?
good lord
mori's bored
welcome to the killing floor!
life ain't ever fair, but hold up then, what's this?
naturally that means death is justice!
lemme liberate you
世界がhates you
we can make 'em pay too!
ban-ba-ba-ban!
the end is nigh end is nigh
didn't get the memo yet? end is nigh
girls, line up single file
wanna end the world in style
get on some armageddon stuff like
gotta kill 'em allから end is nigh
checkmate, i'm a superstar
stay insane, but you rock with it
like 24/7 i'm a hot mess ya love-hate
Like 24/7, I'm a hot mess, you love-hate,
get less boring, oh my god!!
ホームラン、バタバタ swing my shot
Home run, flailing, swing my shot,
like a villainous villainess, bring home the jackpot
勇者も悪役も変わらない
Heroes and villains are no different,
派手にブチかまそうぜ
let's make a flashy spectacle out of it.
life’s just a tightrope, why not stop to fool around?
Life's just a tightrope, why not stop to fool around?
"chaotic good" is peak right now i can show ya how
don’t get confused, we are not the same i’m a ruthless dame
"good vs evil" is so overdone let’s all kick back and party just leave it to moi
loosen my lips loosen my li-li-lips that’s karma
loosen my lips i’m about to say some ish, get it
that’s karma
sorry i’m just better sorry we’re go-getters
ain’t my fault we’re wicked, stunning, tricky why you running?
bet’cha think you’re clever whatever!
talk about a “kumbaya”
Talk about a "kumbaya."
フルボックン ボッチゃって 欲望 召し上がれ
Full boxin', bottchatte, feast on desire.
アイ ＄ ハート get down ウィンク
I $ heart, get down, wink.
see yonara サイコ ですわ
See ya later, it's psycho.
ドメスティック
Domestic,
ドラマティック
dramatic,
愛しき 人々
beloved people,
この指とまれ
gather at this finger.
ハードに ハートは ハイになって 弾けて
Hardly, the heart gets high and bursts.
恥ずかしさ 捨てちまえ 叫び 踊り 誇れ
Throw away the embarrassment, shout, dance, and be proud.
激動的 show 体 酔いしれて ちょーだい
Turbulent show body, get intoxicated, please.
道化の パラダイス
Paradise of fools.
惹かれ合う 感覚が 共鳴 共鳴
The feelings drawn to each other resonate, resonate.
Oh, where am I?
Hang on. Hang on, guys.
Where are my dead beats? Where—I think I found them. Hang on.
My dead beats.
Oh gosh, I feel like I have to go pick up my special camera. My special camera, I left it.
I left it at the other place.
Yeah, that performance was a little too hot, you guys. I think it destroyed—
it destroyed the computer, it destroyed VRC, it destroyed everything.
That's how hot of a performance that was. Hold on, let's—I bet we can cut through here really quick
to get my camera.
Well, you guys know how it's been the past five years, there's always a little surprise guest.
Some scuff.
I like to believe that EN has moved on from all of that, but occasionally it will creep back up on me.
That's okay, no problem.
I'm gonna grab my camera.
Okay, where to go?
Quite the workout.
But I got it.
Hello.
As you can see, I'm um...
What if we just...
I think I've got the power to teleport.
Oh!
Okay.
Let me get the camera.
What do you guys think of the Hell Temple?
I figure maybe we can move right along though.
Um, there are some secrets around the Hell Temple
that I think we'll leave for a little bit later, but for now I wanted to say, do you guys see that hand over here?
that we'll leave for later. Do you see that hand?
What is this?
This is some end of the world stuff.
This is some end-of-the-world stuff.
Look at that.
You see that hand? It's just what's the hand doing there?
You see that hand? What's it even doing there?
What if I were to stand on the hand and do some poses?
What if I stood on the hand and did some poses?
Maybe we can get some poses of me...
standing on the hand.
This is like some... some Evangelion stuff, you know?
This is like some Evangelion stuff, you know?
It's just me and my skeleton at the end of the world, standing on a hand.
Just me and my skeleton at the end of the world.
What the hand doing? What the hand doing?
Let me pull my deadbeats closer to me.
Hang on a sec.
Okay.
Pull, I'm pulling you closer. I'm reeling you in like you're a fish on a hook.
I'm pulling you in like a fish on a hook.
Giant Skelly!
Yeah, let's grab some screenshots if you want.
This is Mori Calliope posing on a hand.
Wait, I should do something super whimsical.
What if I did a pose with like no eyeballs or something?
What if I did a pose with, like, no eyeballs?
Hang on.
'Cause that could be fun. No eyes.
What's she doing?
What's she doing on the hand?
Did you know I could stretch my leg this far?
Oh god, I'm gonna fall!
No, it's no problem.
I'm just being super whimsical. I'm being super whimsical.
I'm just being super whimsical.
Do a backflip. I can't.
I can't. The tracking's just too... too good over here. It's too good.
The tracking's just too good over here.
It's not possible.
I'm... I'm too busy doing real body tracking.
I'm too busy doing real body tracking.
Anyway, you guys wanna... wanna get my eyes back?
Anyway, do you guys wanna get my eyes back?
Ugh, it's been a crazy day, huh?
Well, let's... let's go ahead and check out the city because there's some stuff here that I wanted to look at, so
Let's go check out the city I wanted to look at.
Not just the hand, but
Check this out. What is this little arena over here? With all this... debris.
check this out. What is this little arena here?
It's actually the word is debris.
Actually, the word is debris.
Uh, maybe we can get a better look.
Maybe we can get a better look.
Hang on. Would you guys like a better look at this place? 'Cause I would like a better look at this place.
Would you guys like a better look at this place?
So what if we... Oh.
Hey guys, I found one of those camera thingies.
Uh, if I press this button, we might be able to get
If I press this button, we might be able to get...
Ooh!
Check it. It's a dilapidated... dilapidated city.
Check it. It's a dilapidated city.
Is that... is that Big Papa Deadbeat?
Is that Big Papa Deadbeat?
Could that be the Papa Reaper up there?
Was that event held here? You would think, right?
That's the kind of vibe that I'm getting from this place, this dilapidated city.
That's the vibe I'm getting from this city.
And that's the deadbeat being chained by his neck.
Maybe we could save them.
Maybe we could save him.
I feel bad.
That's actually my house.
Oh god, I'm sorry, Deadbeat! I didn't mean to... to show your house like that in front of everybody.
Oh god, I'm sorry, Deadbeat. I didn't mean to.
Oh, I'm sorry. Wait, that was an accident.
Oh, but look, this... people really could live here. Would I choose to live, maybe I should build my house here.
People really could live here. Would I choose to live—
maybe I should build my house here.
'Cause I'm looking into building a house, right?
Deadbeats, I mentioned that.
Maybe I should build my house here.
Oh, you guys want to see something cool actually?
There's still... there's something that I haven't showed you I can do with this outfit.
There's something I haven't showed you with this outfit.
You're really close.
I'm really close to you.
Hi.
Uh... check this out.
Um... check this out.
Hold on.
I'm... I'm changing, don't look.
Okay.
Here we go.
No jacket.
No-jacket Mori Calliope!
Check it out! My hands' doing funny things.
Check it out! My hands are doing funny things.
Did you know that I have... I have 50 extra tendons in my hands?
Did you know I have 50 extra tendons in my hands?
Uh, peace sign. We do peace.
Uh, peace sign. Let's do peace.
Peace.
Handicam.
Gasp! My shoulders exposed!
Gasp! My shoulders are exposed!
No way.
It looks pretty cool though. Perfect for summertime, right?
It looks pretty cool though. Perfect for summer, right?
Although I get the feeling if I put on the beanie, I would definitely look like a robber in that case.
Though if I put on the beanie, I'd look like a robber.
What can you do?
Nothing much. Summer just ended.
Did it, really?
I don't feel like it's ended.
I feel like we still got a ways to go.
But back to the relevant subject here... back to the relevant subject. We're in this dilapidated city.
Back to the relevant subject... the dilapidated city.
And it's cool. I'd love to just rest my legs,
It's cool. I'd love to rest my legs,
but I feel like another memory's coming on.
You know?
Another like, I've been here before and sang some songs with some friends.
Like I've been here before and sang songs with friends.
So, would you guys like to see that?
Maybe we can both have a brain blast together.
Maybe we can have a brain blast together.
Channel your... your third eye, channel the inner part of your brain to remember things that you forgot.
Channel your third eye, channel your inner brain.
do more often.
It'll be very helpful for me.
But anyway, um, let's go ahead and run the memory!
Cut your mother ties
This ain't the only battlefield I can televise
Ego is an armor, so put the camera down and face it
They went and got complacent
Kill 'em all and run with air. You say you stand for nothing, no one else can relate.
Just know the company you keep is in the business of hate. Are you afraid? Run away.
I'm close to getting paid
I'll be dancing on my own in a bulletproof vest
Go ahead, shoot, shoot, shoot hard, baby, did you miss? Ricochet, ricochet!
You've been thinking about me any time, of any day
Forget your street fights, this a trench war
I'll make you mosh, mosh, mosh till you hit the floor. Getting thirsty for collision, let them wonder what they're missing in the front row!
Lock and load, now here we go.
This ain't no lifeline, it's a call to arms.
Become the risen, the unforgiven. Make a decision, if you're looking for permission to riot, you got it wrong.
Say goodbye to your identity, click-clash, now you belong.
The situation isn't fluid at all. Took out my riders, paintballs, and markers, and I ruined the wall. It's not that complicated, I could choose to run, but I crawl.
Just let the ankles of the skeptics do a wobbly and we fall.
I'll be dancing on my own in a bulletproof vest
Go ahead, shoot, shoot, shoot hard, baby, did you miss? Ricochet, ricochet!
You've been thinking about me any time, of any day.
Forget your street fights, this a trench war.
I'll make you mosh, mosh, mosh till you hit the floor. Getting thirsty for collision,
let them wonder what they're missing in the front row! Lock and load!
Now here we go. This ain't no lifeline, it's a call to arms.
Become the risen, the unforgiven. Make a decision, if you're looking for permission to riot, you got it wrong.
Say goodbye to your identity, click-clash, now you belong.
I'll be dancing on my own in a bulletproof vest.
They can shoot, shoot, shoot and we'll see it shoot past.
Fighting all our battles, know the current too well. They go every set rage and they follow us to hell.
Finger on the trigger, about to conquer and run.
Got a lyric in the chamber, but I'm aiming my gun!
Forget your street fights, this a trench war.
I'll make you mosh, mosh, mosh till you hit the floor. Getting thirsty for collision,
let them wonder what they're missing in the front row! Lock and load!
Now here we go. This ain't no lifeline,
it's a call to arms. Become the risen, the unforgiven.
Make a decision, if you're looking for permission to riot, you got it wrong. Say goodbye to your identity, click-clash, now you belong.
Fading echoes, lying, torn, and onward looking.
Stepping up to play the coward, stepping by someone you devoured.
It's a sick and twisted, miscreant existence!
Fading echoes, lying, torn, and onward looking.
Stepping up to play the coward, stepping by someone you devoured.
It's a sick and twisted, miscreant existence!
Override, override, errors creeping through the core,
protocols failing
override, override
system collapse in 3, 2, 1
Inside my mind, noises that plague and repeat
Trust? Faith? Just go ahead and delete
No morals, justice, they are merely a code. Shut it down, I rewrite what is mine.
Override, override, override is mine!
Consume my soul as if it's a parasite
Just one shot that will penetrate in delight
Fake hope? Dead end? Wrong code? Glitched mind? Rewrite, rewrite, rewrite, rewrite!
What it may take away from me, may it try and destroy me
Don't worry, I keep on fighting through to defy, and move on.
Let the chaos ensue once again. Override, override!
Come and set fire to the zero light that burns so bright
A world where only ruins exist. Survival is not just a myth.
No rewind, no reset, there is a flower that will bloom beyond what's up ahead.
It's not a loop, it's the 1 that I choose. I fall, I rise, I override!
override...
errors creeping through the core
protocols failing
override... override...
system collapse in 3, 2, 1
無数のノイズ、脳内がバグる
Countless noises, my brain is bugging out.
trust? faith? そんなのはdelete
Trust? Faith? Delete all of that.
モラルも正義も単なるコード
Morals and justice are just mere codes.
shut it down, i rewrite what is mine
精神蝕むparasite
A parasite gnawing at my spirit.
just one shot脳天突き抜ける
Just one shot piercing straight through my mind.
fake hope? dead end? wrong code? glitched mind?
rewrite × rewrite × rewrite × rewrite!!
何度奪われても
No matter how many times it's taken,
何度壊されても
no matter how many times it's destroyed,
それでもまだ
even still,
戦え 扛え 進め
I will fight, resist, and press on!
混沌を宿して
Embodying chaos,
override , override
override, override.
“0”の光放つ火をつけろ
Ignite the light that shines from "0"!
この壊れた世界で
In this broken world,
“証明”を叫ぶ
I scream out my "proof."
no rewind , no reset
No rewind, no reset,
カオスの先に咲く花がある
there is a flower blooming beyond the chaos.
ループじゃない 選んだ“1”だ
It's not a loop, it's the "1" I chose!
i fall , i rise , i override
I fall, I rise, I override,
we fall , we rise , we override!
we fall, we rise, we override!
fading echoes filling the air
can't expect 'em all to fight fair
lost inside nightmares
hack the fear , strip it bare
hack the fear, strip it bare.
glitched emotions , vacant stares
Glitched emotions, vacant stares,
in the end , it 's goin' nowhere
in the end, it's goin' nowhere.
drown in loops , what 's the truth?
Drown in loops, what's the truth?
rise again and break the chains!!
叫ぶ記憶はfirewall
The screaming memories are a firewall,
just one more step 焦げつくリアル
just one more step into the scorched reality.
cry out? break down? lost cause? broken dream?
rewire × rewire × rewire × rewire!!
何度散らばっても
No matter how many times we scatter,
何度閉ざされても
no matter how many times we are shut away,
この手でまだ
with these hands, once again
繋げ 描け 掴め
we connect, depict, and seize!
終焉を飛び越え
Flying past our demise,
override , override
override, override.
灰の中から光を掴め
Seize the light from amidst the ashes,
この無慈悲な夜に
into this merciless night,
“真実”をかざせ
hold up the "truth"!
no rewind , no reset
No rewind, no reset,
選ばれぬ道にも咲く花よ
flowers bloom even on unchosen paths.
ループじゃない 生まれた“1”だ
It's not a loop, I was born a "1"!
i fall , i rise , i override
I fall, I rise, I override,
we fall , we rise , we override!
we fall, we rise, we override!
崩壊した世界で
In the collapsed world,
声だけが響いた
only our voices echoed.
dead code を焼き尽くせ
Burn dead code to ashes,
限界を蹴り飛ばせ
kick away all limitations,
宿命をねじ伏せろ
and subjugate destiny!
zero out all despair now
override , override
override, override.
“0”の核心(コア)へ響く声上げろ
Raise your voice echoing to the core of "0",
この痛みを描いて
embracing this pain,
最果てへ向かえ
head toward the very edge!
no rewind , no reset
No rewind, no reset,
カオスの先に咲く花がある
there is a flower blooming beyond the chaos.
ループじゃない 選んだ“1”だ
It's not a loop, it's the "1" I chose!
i fall , i rise , i override
I fall, I rise, I override,
we fall , we rise , we override!
we fall, we rise, we override!
lalalalala...
Do you guys remember when Nerissa Ravencroft died?
Cuz I do!
'Cause I do!
Oh, these have been really fun, these memories.
I really enjoyed looking through them with you guys.
I saw somebody in chat said, "Help, is she on desktop?"
No, she's in the world with us!
But, you know, a desktop is very helpful for folks who cannot, who cannot be present in the exact place,
or do not have to have full-body capabilities at the moment.
But, you know, I think despite all the technical, technical walls that we've had, you know, bringing this nostalgic trip down memory lane to light,
But, you know, I think despite all the technical walls that we've had, bringing this nostalgic trip down memory lane to light,
everything, everything has been so interesting and fun
everything has been so interesting and fun
the whole time, and and I'm just so happy to be able to spin that with you guys, here to show you guys this amazing creation.
the whole time, and I'm just so happy to be able to share that with you guys, here to show you guys this amazing creation.
Look at that deadbeat!
Look at me and me and the dead- Deadbeat, you'll be shy. Come back.
Look at me and the dead— Deadbeat, you'll be shy, come back.
There's a deadbeat.
There's the deadbeat.
That's a deadbeat.
That's a deadbeat for you.
Mori Calliope peak. I like that.
Can we start using that? You can if you want
I won't- I won't say it, but if if you want to.
I won't- I won't say it, but if you want to.
It makes me happy.
It makes me happy that you enjoy- What if I jump? I'm jumping.
It makes me happy that you enjoy— What if I jump? I'm jumping.
See if that makes a difference in in anything.
See if that makes a difference in anything.
Like if the camera can really handle the the full capacity of my jumps.
Like if the camera can really handle the full capacity of my jumps.
And anyway, we're kind of- we don't have all the time in the world, but, you know, we- if we want to look at secrets,
And anyway, we don't have all the time in the world, but, you know, if we want to look at secrets,
you want to look at the secrets, we probably got to get moving a little bit.
if we want to look at the secrets, we probably got to get moving a little bit.
But there's one- there's one special secret that I want to look at
But there's one special secret that I want to look at
before we move on to the faded Atlantis that I'm really excited about checking out.
Do you guys want to go?
If you don't know where it is, you may have noticed, if you look yonder, if you look o- way over there,
If you don't know where it is, you may have noticed, if you look yonder, if you look way over there,
you can see that there's a black square in the the in the cliffside.
you can see that there's a black square in the cliffside.
Way over there, in the cliffside of the plaza.
So I was thinking maybe we could go there.
There's a little secret over here, perhaps it leads to another memory.
I don't know, I'm kind of nervous. I feel like what if this- well, what if what if we're not able to get back?
I don't know, I'm kind of nervous. I feel like, what if we're not able to get back?
the ominous square in the wall
Typically if you see a square hidden wall, visions of hidden walls, maybe I should roll through like Dark Souls,
Wakanda forever
anyway, anyway,
Shall we go inside?
Whoa!
Hey.
I know this place.
Do you guys know this place? Do you guys remember?
Oh man, it's been a really long time, huh?
I know it. Some of you were around for for this, but remember when we had
I know it. Some of you were around for this, but remember when we had
one of our aw
and see the banner, Happy HoloMyth 2 year anniversary.
last from the past, right? The memories.
blast from the past, right? The memories.
Remember when we all sang and danced in an interesting way on this stage?
And I remember we had so many things to announce back then and we did it in 360 too.
So, like people could could use their phone and like sit in the center and like rotate it around
So people could use their phone and sit in the center and rotate it around,
and they could look at their oshi the whole time. I wonder how many deadbeats were looking mostly at Mori.
You don't have to though because there there're so many wonderful people to enjoy and support, but, but if you did look at me lots, I'd I'd be really happy.
You don't have to though because there are so many wonderful people to enjoy and support, but if you did look at me lots, I'd be really happy.
I want to do something like that again someday, actually. And walking around this old place and thinking that to myself, you know, like,
I want to do something like that again someday, actually. Walking around this old place and thinking that to myself, you know, like,
it would be really cool to to do something like that again.
it would be really cool to do something like that again.
And we can't forget the backstage, right? You you guys were allowed backstage, which is
And we can't forget the backstage, right? You guys were allowed backstage, which is
very special, don't you think? Hold on.
Whoa! Remember we had you guys sit We had you guys sit right there on this stool, in this exact spot,
back in the day.
It's all kind of dark and dimly lit.
Since it was so so long ago, and somehow it still feels like home, you know?
Since it was so long ago, and somehow it still feels like home, you know?
I really love I'd love for you guys to be able to visit this spot, too. But, maybe you'll be able to.
I really love—I'd love for you guys to be able to visit this spot, too. But maybe you'll be able to.
Well, we'll talk about that a little bit later, but I guess we better get out of here. We got we got an Atlantis to look at.
So, let's get let's get moving, I guess. As much as I would love to sit here and just reminisce about
So let's get moving, I guess. As much as I would love to sit here and reminisce about
everything that's happened, right?
I think maybe we should go ahead and get moving.
Before I get too sentimental.
All right. Well, let's go.
I'm happy you're with us, Callie. I'm happy I'm here. Thank you for making it fun to be here.
Well, well, it's a happy occasion, right? We should be we should be happy and
Well, it's a happy occasion, right? We should be happy and
excited for the future. So, let's let's go.
excited for the future. So let's go.
We're going, we're going. But a moment of quiet reflection is fun too, don't you think? I think so.
Uh the way to Atlantis is kind of far, so I hope you guys can keep up with me. Get running, deadbeats. We're running, we're running.
The way to Atlantis is kind of far, so I hope you guys can keep up with me. Get running, deadbeats! We're running, we're running.
All this training I've been doing and I still feel like I'm not in enough shape to be doing this. But we're going, we're going. Atlantis time. Atlantis time.
Let's go, let's go, let's go. Yikes. Oh, here we are. Ta-da.
Okay, this is another one of those ugh. Honey. Nice.
Check this out. Whoa! That's Atlantis. Atlantis finally, at last! We get to see it.
I feel like this is based off of a room of a good friend of mine.
Do you guys remember Gura's Atlantis room that was based off of her?
Kind of makes me think of that. Hey, but what the heck is Council? Is that Council Riss?
Kind of makes me think of that. Hey, but what the heck is Council? Is that CouncilRissa?
It might be CouncilRiss, I'm not totally sure, but before we jump in there,
It might be CouncilRissa, I'm not totally sure, but before we jump in there,
I'm getting the feeling that I've entered this place before.
Well, shall we go ahead and take a look at another musical couple of musical memories before we get too deep into exploring, shall we?
All right, deadbeats, play. Run. Run the memory. I'm having a brain, if you could get into the past
First, here it comes!
Huh? Is this supposed to be Atlantis?
Eh, so many memories.
I remember Atlantis. I remember all the places that we had in the original, the original VRC Myth map.
This brings back a lot of memories. There's something kind of different though,
right? There's something kind of different about this place.
Uh, like, um...
Who are those people over there?
Well, they know these people. Familiar faces all around me. Familiar faces...
I want to sing a song with someone here, though. Who will I sing with here, I wonder?
Wait, I see a rock.
There's a rock way up there.
I see a rock.
There's a rock way up there! I'm coming down!
Yeah, come on! Yeah, no problem. There's a lot of stairs.
There's a lot of... Oh, okay.
I guess she doesn't care about the stairs. Oh god, ah!
Dang, you freaking came in like a wrecking ball there.
Hi, babe!
You're so small.
You want a new outfit? Look at you! You look so nice.
Thank you. My brand-new... my brand-new digs. What do you think? My new gear?
Whoa! Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Whoa there, don't get too close there, Skipper. Hold on a second.
How's he?
No, no, no, no. You're like not the first person to do this today, I think. Oh god.
You want a new outfit? Look at you! You look so nice.
Thank you! I appreciate... You look... We look like we're in the same band or something like that.
What the heck? Look at her, she's voguing! Oh my god, I can vogue too.
Ha! Ha! Ha! Ha!
But, you know what? Babe, I think we should sing a song together. Do you want to sing a song?
We should sing... We should sing something really intense. We should sing like a hard rock song, if you want.
Like camping?
Uh, no, no, no camping, no camping. Um...
You get it 'cause intense, like camping?
God. Babe! Stop!
You're reminding me of Ina right now with the puns. Oh my god, I should smack you,
but I won't. I'll be serious.
Let's do something serious.
Yeah, just a little. It doesn't have to be too serious, you know, just serious enough, right?
All right.
Let's run it, then.
Play music.
テメェの所為です
It's your fault.
どの娘が好き？？
Which girl do you like??
この子に決めた
I've chosen this girl.
角度を調節
Adjusting the angle,
覚悟微調節
fine-tuning my resolve.
飽きたらポイから
Once I'm bored, I toss 'em.
Place any bets
Decide who is special and discard the rest
Gambler by nature
Chips start to stack
Racing lovely animals until they crack
やいのやいの
Yelling and shouting,
貼り付け parasite
clinging parasite.
ヤンデレッテレル
Yandere-tereterel
テメェの所為です
It's all your fault.
Black out, break down
Toss it when you've had enough
やっちゃえ いっちゃえ
Do it, go for it!
I can tell you're not impressed
右向け右
Face to the right,
左向け左
face to the left.
Leave the defective, unworthy of investment
飽きたらポイから
Once I'm bored, I toss 'em,
hot mess, worthless doll
よってたかっていやがらせ
Ganging up and harassing!
Gambler by nature
Chips start to stack
Racing lovely animals until they crack
Beautiful dreams await modest hearts
Close your eyes and all you'll see is black
才能
Talent
サイコパスと紙一重
is a hair's breadth from a psychopath.
やっちまったの後悔で fever
Regretting what I've done, I've got fever
もういい！
Enough already!
starving!
時間の無駄 無駄
What a waste of time!
やっちゃえ いっちゃえ
Do it, go for it!
I can tell you're not impressed
ウゼェ バカ アホ カス
Annoying, stupid, idiot, scum!
こちとら 最下層
We're at the very bottom.
どうにかなりそう
Feels like anything could happen,
どうにでもなりそう
feels like anything goes.
ぶっとい 絆
A thick, unbreakable bond
lonely lonely
trouble in paradise
oh, if only
愛を歌って
Singing about love,
「あいうえお」から「ん」まで昇って
ascending from "A-I-U-E-O" to "N"
見下してやるわ
I'll look down on you!
やいのやいの
Yelling and shouting,
貼り付け parasite
clinging parasite.
ヤンデレッテレル
Yandere-tereterel
テメェの所為です
It's all your fault.
Black out, break down
Toss it when you're out of love
やっちゃえ いっちゃえ
Do it, go for it!
i'm the one that's not impressed
テメェの所為です
It's all your fault.
責任とりなはれ
Take responsibility for it.
パッと光って
Flashing brilliantly,
華 開く わ
flowers bloom.
ヒリヒリ先を削りながら
While scraping away at the burning edges...
削り合い削られてって削りながら
scraping against each other, being worn down...
Woah, woah...
Guess I took a leap, no turning back point to go
Looking deep inside for the cheat to exploit, you know
あいつもこいつもどいつもこいつも
Even this one, that one, that one, and this one
Driving me crazy, yeah
Wanted, wasted
Sorry lookin' faced kid
Can't stop falling down
Tell me how I'm worthless, show ya where the dirt is
One man's trash is another man's purpose
Day one, flying high
Come tomorrow, let me die
Talk trash, choke and whine
Nothing I own is truly mine
ごっくん
Gulp.
愛されたいのに 会えない夢を見ているのはなんで？
Even though I want to be loved, why do I see dreams I can't reach?
変えたい現実 胸糞悪くて
I want to change this reality, it feels so disgusting
Highになる
I get high
やっちゃって やっちゃって やっちゃって そのままで傷つけちゃって
Just do it, do it, do it, just leave it damaged like that
期待裏切る bad ending
A bad ending that betrays expectations
円から抜け出せない エンドロール
An end roll where I can't escape the circle
演者は揃いも揃って クズに仕立て上げてちょうだい
The performers are all gathered, make me into trash
整合性 正当性 正義の名の下
Consistency, legitimacy, in the name of justice
下ろしてやるわ
I'll bring it down
Game maker, undertaker 脳天直下 くらえ
Game maker, undertaker, take this right on the crown
アンアン 響け mayday, mayday
Ah-ah, let it ring, mayday, mayday
タンタン タンタン 鳴らす
Tan, tan, tan, tan, ringing out
聞こえないふりして 逃げられると思ってんの？
Are you thinking you can escape by pretending you can't hear?
愛されたいのに 会えない夢を見ているのはなんで？
Even though I want to be loved, why do I see dreams I can't reach?
変えたい現実 胸糞悪くて
I want to change this reality, it feels so disgusting
Highになる
I get high
不埒な声で あいつの声は 天国に近そうな気がしてた
With a vulgar voice, his/her voice felt like it was close to heaven
Alright, all night Anger
狂おしく 舞い上がれ
Madly flying up
OMG! OMG! お前が お前が
OMG! OMG! You, you
OMG! OMG! お前が
OMG! OMG! You
OMG! OMG! お前が お前が
OMG! OMG! You, you
OMG! OMG! 傷つけちゃって
OMG! OMG! Leaving it damaged
足らない 足らない 足らない
Not enough, not enough, not enough
足らない 足らない 足らない 足らない カルマ
Not enough, not enough, not enough, karma
あーもううざったい どうにかしてくんないノマシ
Ah, it's so annoying, can't you do something about it?
愛されたいのに 会えない夢を見ているのはなんで？
Even though I want to be loved, why do I see dreams I can't reach?
変えたい現実 胸糞悪くて
I want to change this reality, it feels so disgusting
Highになる
I get high
不埒な声で あいつの声は 天国に近そうな気がしてた
With a vulgar voice, his voice felt like it was close to heaven
Alright, all night Anger
狂おしく 舞い上がれ
Madly flying up
足らない 足らない 足らない 足らない 足らない 足らない
Not enough, not enough, not enough...
カルマ
Karma
愛されたいのに 会えない夢を見ているのはなんで？
Even though I want to be loved, why do I see dreams I can't reach?
変えたい現実 胸糞悪くて
I want to change this reality, it feels so disgusting
Highになる
I get high
不埒な声で あいつの声は 天国に近そうな気がしてた
With a vulgar voice, his voice felt like it was close to heaven
Alright, all night Anger
狂おしく 舞い上がれ
Madly flying up
足らない 足らない 足らない 足らない 足らない 足らない カルマ
Not enough, not enough, not enough, karma
足らない 足らない 足らない 足らない 足らない 足らない
Not enough, not enough, not enough...
カルマ
Karma
足らない 足らない 足らない 足らない 足らない 足らない
Not enough, not enough, not enough...
カルマ
Karma
足らない 足らない 足らない 足らない 足らない 足らない
Not enough, not enough, not enough...
カルマ
Karma
足らない 足らない 足らない 足らない 足らない 足らない
Not enough, not enough, not enough...
Yeah, yeah, Deadbeats, I know you saw that...
you saw Steph's on flying around with the mute button.
Can you guess which, which memory song we, we sung first?
Can't guess which memory song we sang first?
But in all seriousness, in all seriousness,
But in all seriousness...
I want to give a huge shoutout to all the staff that worked really, really hard on all of this,
I want to give a huge shoutout to all the staff who worked really, really hard on all of this,
because, honestly, this, this entire production,
because, honestly, this entire production...
the whole team like in studio has been like five people, and then everybody working on it behind the scenes is like three or so.
the whole team in studio was like five people, and everyone behind the scenes was like three or so.
Compare that to like the the 30 plus people that work on the really high quality productions that they do for birthdays and stuff like that.
Compare that to the 30 plus people working on the high-quality productions for birthdays and things like that.
You know, you're one you're one you only get to do one, right?
You know, you only get to do one, right?
Which is why I'm so glad that we did this together,
Which is why I'm so glad we did this together,
and I'm so grateful that it turned out the way that it did.
and I'm so grateful it turned out the way it did.
But but but hold on a sec. Look, I want you to look, oh god, my jacket, oh, jacket.
But, but... hold on a sec. Look, I want you to look—oh god, my jacket! Oh, jacket!
Look at everyone, it's council risk, like this is a bit of a smaller a smaller little performance area compared to the others.
Look at everyone, it's CouncilRissa! This is a bit of a smaller performance area compared to the others.
But look at that girl, Triton!
Although I will say, lady in the bag, is that supposed to be Gura? cuz there are some differences. I'm sure that you all can...
Although I will say, lady in the bag, is that supposed to be Gura? 'Cause there are some differences. I'm sure that you all can...
Not now, not now.
Not now.
But you never know.
I don't really know if that's something that she cared very much about, but...
I don't really know if that's something
that she cared very much about, but...
Catching strays, catching strays.
Nah, but I I look really angry. Hold on. Why do I-- Oh! There we go!
Nah, but I look really angry. Hold on.
Why do I-- Oh! There we go!
Oh man. I hope that-- I hope that my friends who...
Oh man. I hope that-- I hope that
my friends who...
are no longer active with us anymore, are living their best lives out there, and
are no longer active with us anymore,
are living their best lives out there,
doing amazing cool stuff, wherever they are, you know?
and doing amazing, cool stuff,
wherever they are, you know?
That's what I want more than anything.
That would make me happy.
A lot of those faces around us here too. I really appreciate them.
A lot of those faces around us here, too.
I really appreciate them.
I'm glad I got to get to know them.
And I'll keep watching them in my own way, in my heart.
And I'll keep watching them in my own way,
in my heart.
Stop getting sentimental on us!
We're getting later into the stream, so it's happening. We got to move along, though.
We're getting later into the stream,
so it's happening. We got to move along.
We got to move along 'cause there's something that I really-- I really think I need to show you.
We got to move along 'cause there's
something I really need to show you.
There's something really cool.
Follow-- follow me!
Off we go! We're-- we're moving, we're-- we're moving on up! We're going, we're going-- out of here!
Off we go! We're moving, we're moving
on up! We're going-- out of here!
There's-- oh, but really quick, I wanted to mention something. And I think that this
There's-- oh, but really quick,
I wanted to mention something.
might be a good place for me to announce this. There's a-- something-- there's a little secret
And I think this is a good place
to announce this. There's a little secret
something something below this area. It's related to Mori. It's related to Mori, but there's a little-- a little secret for Deadbeats
below this area. It's related to Mori,
but there's a little secret for Deadbeats
to check out underneath this stage. What-- how would you be able to check it out though if we didn't see it today?
to check out underneath this stage.
How would you be able to check it out
Well, that's because the plan is to release this world in the next few days
if we didn't see it today? Well, that's
because the plan is to release this world
to you guys, so that you can hang out here with your friends and explore around
in the next few days to you guys,
so that you can hang out here with friends
and just chill together, and it'll be so fun! I hope that you guys will
and explore around and just chill together,
and it'll be so fun! I hope that you guys
have a good time with it and explore and find little secrets, um, like what we found
will have a good time and explore
and find little secrets, like what we found
or what we're finding today, so make sure that you get a chance to, and we'll make sure that you guys know where to access it and find it.
today. So make sure you get a chance to,
and we'll make sure you know where to find it.
So that'll be really fun.
Um, let's go, let's go. Still things I want to show you.
Let's go, let's go!
Still things I want to show you.
Oh man, how-- oh! You know what? This is the place over here that-- that I was most interested in
Oh man, how-- oh! You know what?
This is the place over here that
running towards.
I was most interested in running towards.
Come on, come on, come on, let's go, let's go. We're moving, we're shmoving. Here we go!
Come on, let's go! We're moving,
we're shmoving. Here we go!
Guys, did any of you guys see this in the distance? The-- the-- the desert? The-- the desert!
Guys, did any of you guys see this
in the distance? The-- the desert!
The desert! The nerd run!
Hey, don't set-- that's not true!
Hey, that's not true!
It's a very cool run!
It's a very cool run I'm doing right now.
No, no, no, my walking on the water, no, that's totally-- No, Chad, don't worry, it's just-- Jeez.
No, my walking on the water, no, that's--
No, Chad, don't worry, it's just-- jeez.
No, I'm not-- I'm not J-man-- No, Chad, wrong, wrong, wrong.
No, I'm not-- I'm not J-Man---
No, Chad, wrong, wrong, wrong.
Do you all? Yo, am I desert? Question mark, question mark, question mark? Yes.
Am I in a desert??? Yes.
It looks kind of gray right now.
That's an Ome desert. That's the Ome desert over there.
That's an Ome desert.
That's the Ome desert over there.
And that big clock? Do you guys think--
do you think there may be something behind the clock?
do you think there may be something
behind the clock?
Because I want to go find out. I want to see how far I can-- I can dive into this place, but I get the feeling we might find something nice.
Because I want to go find out. I want to
see how far I can dive into this place.
Really quick. Hold on a sec.
I get the feeling we might find
something nice. Hold on a sec.
Oh, I'm excited! I'm excited! What are we going to find?
Oh, I'm excited! I'm excited!
What are we going to find?
Uh bus stop? Question mark? There is a bus stop in the middle of the desert. We built one together in Minecraft--
A bus stop? There is a bus stop
in the middle of the desert!
I knew it! It's a dimensional door!
Guys, look!
I found a dimensional door!
Though I kind of had a feeling it would be here, and I may have gotten told by the powers that be that there was something back here.
Though I kind of had a feeling it would
be here, and the powers that be told me.
But shall we go take a look together?
Shall we go take a look together?
Let me take off this beanie, I'm sick of looking like a rob-- It's very cute though.
Let me take off this beanie, I'm sick
of looking like a rob-- it's very cute though.
I mean, I-- the idea was mind to have the beanie on.
I mean, the idea was mine
to have the beanie on.
Let's go into space together.
What, darkness? No, no, no, no.
Whoa! We're in space!
Is it okay for me to be walking on this floor?
Is it okay for me to be walking
on this floor?
I'm not going to die, right?
Hey! Is this the original bus stop?
This is the original desert bus stop, it feels like.
This is the original desert bus stop,
it feels like.
And everything is in the same-- the same kind of lower-poly style.
And everything is in the same--
the same kind of lower-poly style.
Another bus stop? Bus is stopped.
And then in here, something familiar?
Whoa! Holomyth one year.
In a timeline...
This I didn't...
This is the original place.
We've got the Ina room...
I feel like I shouldn't be allowed to be here, but
I want to sit down for like a cup of tea.
In the original!
Look at that little Taco Dach being so good.
And all Ina's paintings for all of us.
Amrit's...
crying Yago statue.
Look at him. Look at him cry.
We'll go in there in a second.
Then there's my old room.
You guys remember my old room?
And the moon stage.
Wow, from the hell temple, it's like the same...
The same style and everything.
Remember when I did a smoke concert here?
It's the Mori cave.
It was so fun chilling out here with you guys.
I know it's kind of older now and...
a little worn down, but
I miss this old chill spot.
I wonder if we got all of them here.
Oh, my goodness.
We have time to check out all of them?
We're going to have to move on pretty soon, but
I don't want to. I want to keep looking.
Look, KFP square!
Oh, man.
Do you guys remember all the fun like Easter-themed stuff or like spring-themed stuff that used to happen?
Was there an egg hunt?
I'd like to say there was a VRChat egg hunt once
I'm pretty sure there was a VR Chat egg hunt once
that we did in this kind of place.
And all the little games that we did as well.
Kiara did so much fun VRChat stuff too.
Kiara did so much fun VR Chat stuff too.
If I remember correctly, memory serves,
and I think it does.
Memory serves correctly.
I feel kind of out of place here being in full color, but
I feel old dad's is chat.
Ah, it's not that long ago.
It's only half a decade.
Let's go
to what we got here.
I guess that yeah, there was the Ahmed desert.
And then...
Goombus's room,
which we already we already checked out Atlantis,
but look, you can kind of see...
Everything's kind of older and worn out here.
The pillars too are kind of broken, but
I remember it.
I remember what this place used to look like.
Man, it was so fun getting to explore all the different rooms too.
I can hear right on time right now.
It's really nostalgic.
Well, I hope that you guys get a chance to enjoy
this world, cuz there was so much love put into it by Seafoam.
Thank you so much.
And thank you so much to Melin as well for working so hard on this.
I love it.
I want to do my own exploring later.
And then we can't forget.
You guys, here we are, the original open bar.
It's the bar!
Our old bar where we hung out and
just chatted the days away,
all the silly stupid jokes in our small forms.
Everything's kind of decrepit now,
the beginning, right?
All the memories.
Movie nights.
We had a lot of watch-alongs, didn't we?
Elevator, auditorium.
Oh, my gosh, wait. Hold on.
Happy HoloMyth first anniversary!
Four years ago.
Hi, mom!
Hey, deadbeats!
Look at how much I've grown.
We've all grown, haven't we?
Everybody was crying because we couldn't meet each other.
And then we did.
Half a decade, huh?
We should we should get out of here before I get too emo.
Here, funny walk, funny run.
Ah, so silly!
We got barely any time left, but
I'm sure it'll be okay.
One last thing I wanted to show you is this place.
It's the ship!
Sunfish ship.
You guys remember this place too? Remember our small adventures together?
Oh, man. And we looked out here and we saw saw Sana was so big.
Yeah.
And then of course our captain was driving here.
All adventures...
The sunfish...
Maybe I should take this baby on a joy ride. I'm sure Ame wouldn't mind.
I'm thinking about it, though.
Especially after coming back here.
Well, I think we should quick-transport back to the desert, guys, since we don't have much time left.
I have teleport abilities, though. All I have to do is summon my persona. Okay, here we go.
Um, but I hope you guys get a chance to check this place out in more detail, you know? That would make me really happy.
Ah, we're back!
Because I feel like, after all that we've looked at so far, and all the memories that we've experienced, there's a special song that I want to sing here.
But I have the feeling I already sang it.
Well, then... shall we remember?
Let's go.
Last Days
Castle made of thorns, moon that rose in crimson
Grab for something more, all I get is distance
Driving roadless, feels like the end of a life
Running through those nights, all I saw were curses
Stuck here unalive, floating on the surface
Still and shallow, probably left to rot, I'm sinking
So close to giving up, giving out, giving in
Could I still live again, live again, live again?
But what's the point in fighting when nothing lasts at all?
On your last day, standing here alone with you
I found my vision was way off, way off, yeah
Now I can't wake up, wake up, yeah
Don't tell me it's over, it must be
Is it gonna be just me left behind?
Me and my mind, forever wasting time
Back then there was nothing left to lose
Back then every night was wine and blues
That's when every pen I tried to use
Ended up leaking my weakness and bled through
All in, but still a little mistaken
Faking like I knew the risk taken
Wakin' up every night pacing
Was it all a waste, then?
Am I worth replacing?
Locked down deep in my soul is what I really want to shout
Now, out of control, but I still hold it inside
And now there's nowhere to hide
You wanna know if I'm fine, well
At least nobody's died
So close to giving up, giving out, giving in
Could I still live again, live again, live again?
But what's the point in fighting when nothing lasts at all?
On your last day, standing here alone with you
I found my vision was way off, way off, yeah
Now I can't wake up, wake up, yeah
Don't tell me it's over, it must be
Is it gonna be just me left behind?
Me and my mind
Every now and then, reality creeps in
Every now and then, I glance over the deep end
You'll live on, still, so when I'm not around
Remember me, remember what we found
On our last day, standing here alone
'Cause nothing lasts forever
Wake up, wake up, yeah
No, I can't wake up, wake up, yeah
No, it's not over, it can't be
Is it gonna be just me left behind?
Is this goodbye?
On my last day, doesn't matter where or when
I swear I'll find us a way out, way out, yeah
So let things play out, play out, yeah
'Cause I know some dreams just can't come true
But I wanna see you again sometime
That song in my heart, it kept me alive
Hey there, Deadbeats.
Hey there.
It's me.
It's okay to be sad.
It's okay to miss the people who changed our lives, if they aren't here anymore.
I think...
It's okay.
But as long as we have memories, right?
Um, then I think, maybe, just maybe, it'll be okay.
Even if we never truly move on.
I'm happy that we have memories, right?
And to never, never forget all the stuff that we did together, 'cause we did some really amazing stuff, don't you guys think?
I think we did.
And I don't want to forget any of that 'cause, like I said, I don't really have any plans to get going anytime soon.
But I guess the way that I feel about it is, I'd like to keep remembering...
all those people and things that we did fondly, regardless of anything.
Even through the years, and though they may pass by, and even when the wounds aren't fresh anymore,
I still... I still want to remember.
I know it's hard to... It's hard to move forward sometimes when the things that we love and care about are still behind us, right? Stuck in the past, but...
I'm going to be here to make you smile no matter what, right now.
'Cause there's still stuff I want to do, you know?
And yeah, that's a good point, the good memories, they should make you sad because...
Because that means they were truly good.
We did a lot of really good stuff.
You guys think?
Well, I'm glad that I sang that here with Ina.
I'm really glad.
But there's still some people that I haven't sung with, so...
Let's head to the final area, shall we?
What if I just... bam, teleported myself there...
and use my crazy powers of...
Oh, my waist is broken.
That's okay.
No, it's fine.
All good, all good.
I probably just need to T-pose real quick.
Hey, watch this, watch my sick T-pose.
Hang on, I'm already good at this.
I've become pro at VR Chat in just this short time.
There we go.
Fixed.
All right, time to summon my persona and head to the final area! Oh.
Oof, we're here.
We're here. Oh.
Where did my camera go?
I lost it.
Is it hiding some? Is it behind me?
Oh, I found it.
There you are.
I found you.
Um, this is one of my favorite areas, I think.
You guys...
You guys, look!
What is this? Green fields?
Oh, there's one of those camera thingies.
Hang on. Okay. Uh...
Check this out.
Woah! It's too beautiful!
Can you guys imagine hanging out with your friends here?
Wouldn't that be so awesome?
I'm running up that hill.
I'm running up the hill.
Oh, my gosh!
Wait a minute!
What's this?
Was Ina painting something here?
I didn't know about that!
Hey.
I mean, it is a really nice scenery to paint, I suppose.
I guess it makes sense.
I'd want to paint here.
So expansive. Oh, sorry, feet's on the ground.
Well, that's okay, it doesn't matter.
Um, so surreal and tranquil.
I guess this is a good place to tell you guys the news about...
a special thing that gets released for anniversary, especially. Do you guys know what it is?
Are we going to run the clip?
I think we're going to run the clip.
All right, guys. We have merchandise.
So, I created a little commercial before we get to singing here.
Run it, staff-san!
Man, a song!
It's been five long years together, but we've done it!
We made it to year five together, and while the future's looking pretty crazy and eventful,
let's take a little time to celebrate the story thus far, shall we?
And what better way to do that than with every hololive's bread and butter, the bane of every Deadbeat's wallet:
its existence!
That's right, everybody, it's time for premium goods!
limited, so don't miss out!
Okay!
First, we got a poster.
Duh.
I mean, you guys expect posters by now, I think.
You guys are used to posters from me, and as every good Dead Beat knows, Mori Calliope is a poster fan, and Mori Calliope fans are fans of posters!
I see your rooms.
I know.
Not like in a creepy way or anything, but this one's a bit smaller than the usual huge posters that I always do for these merch drops,
but it's to help with the shipping costs this year.
Uh, I don't know, we'll see, crossing my fingers, but no guarantees, throw it into your cart, see what happens, I guess.
I went for an Underworld Live Show concert poster as a concept here, and my very own Yuki Soumamama created something fun and energetic for the occasion.
So, let's reminisce on the amazing shows that we've gotten to experience together with this big-sized poster!
Yeah, yeah.
Next up.
Oh man, this one is big!
One of my favorite apparel artists, Crisalys, has graced this humble black t-shirt with a high quality and subtle design of your Mori dressed in grimoire attire, playing her bass, probably a little badly in an antique shop.
It's the type of shirt where you'll probably get, you know, compliments from fellow quirky folks,
but the average bystander like wouldn't look twice at you kind of deal.
I don't know, again, I can't guarantee exactly what's going to happen.
Anyway, you might find dead beats out in the wild too, so that's fun.
It's just the kind of shirt that subtly expresses your love for Mori Calliope without being too, you know, in your face, right?
And the design is so, so, so good! I own like five shirts by Crisalys, now I'm about to own six. Anyway, don't miss out.
Next up, it's a Grimoire Plushie! Take her everywhere with you.
That's what seems to be all the rage these days, right? And if you give her a squeeze, she says something.
Uh, I don't know what yet, but maybe we'll all be a little surprised. She's got such a cute and huggable design.
I'm sure she'll make fast friends with your other plushies, especially that weird cat, you know, maybe you can dress her up and put her in a plastic purse for a day out, just have fun, I don't know, be whimsical, whatever you want to do.
Finally, it's a concert and live show staple, a casual wristband.
Show your support for your Mori in your everyday life or at a local show, even if I'm not the one playing.
Something easy to slip on and fun to rock out with.
I want to see all of you guys wearing them at my future shows, okay?
And there's a voice pack, too.
Mori Takes a Break. Huh? What kind of title is that?
It sounds like some fan fiction to me, but give it a listen, I guess. Japanese and English voice available,もちろんあります！
Grab the full set and you will get a foil duplicated stamp on a special postcard.
Be really fast and get your hands on the limited edition set and you might just get your hands on a handwritten autograph from Mori Calliope.
Actually, it's not that you might, you will. You will get a handwritten autograph from Mori Calliope.
If you're fast enough, we always do gold those, so how about I sign it with an extra special pink pen? I don't know, I'll have to see if they let me. Look forward to it!
And again, these are limited to a certain amount.
So, if you want to grab a real autograph from your Mori, do not miss out on this chance.
The sales period will run for about a month, so get your premium goods ASAP, okay?
It's like a full-on concert hall over here between poster, t-shirt, squeezable mini Mori, and wristband.
Get ready for lots more shows together, Deadbeats, and thanks for the unforgettable five years! Love!
Hello.
Thank you so much, everybody. I hope you guys enjoy the goods.
Please look forward to receiving them. They're very cool.
I'm super excited with how they turned out, so make sure that you don't miss it.
I think the shop will open in about six minutes, you'll be able to pre-order your merch and get the limited.
If you're quick, you got to be quick, cuz they do have a limited number.
Um, but yeah, please enjoy, and thank you always for supporting me so much. There will be a members-only encore after this featuring a few more songs and just getting to chat with my members, which I'm excited about.
Um, so please look forward to that.
And there's a new song! I should look a little happier about that.
There's a new song coming out, and I haven't really given any hints about what kind of song it is. People are like, oh, it's going to be so emotional. This looks like an emotional song, but knowing what the song is makes me laugh really hard.
Cuz it's actually a lot simpler than you think.
Something about my early music is that, man, I was so honest, you know? And so I wanted to write a song that not just me myself, I as a person could relate to, but anyone, anyone who has an oshi could relate to.
And so, I hope that you will enjoy it, because it feels like an older Mori song while also being a newer Mori song.
It's hard to explain, but I guess you'll just have to watch it and see. MV is really cute, so we'll watch that premiere together, too.
So don't go anywhere after the credits.
Please look forward to it.
New song, new song.
Let's watch it last,
and, um, share it around, I don't know, if you want, if you like it.
and share it around if you want, if you like it.
Um, but I still have one last song memory to replay in my mind here in this beautiful area.
But I still have one last song memory to replay in my mind here in this beautiful area.
So shall we run it? The last song of today?
Thank you so much, Deadbeats!
Catch you on the flip side.
There might be an after-credits scene.
Let's go!
ああ…
Ah...
Lost in thoughts of frosted frame of mind
Lost in thoughts of a frosted frame of mind,
Honest to God, it's just not our time
Promises flawed by cosmic design
これくらいどうってことない
this much is nothing to fuss about,
でも涙の跡は消せない
but the traces of tears cannot be erased.
Coming of age, the stage doesn't light up
Just right away, they told us it might've
right away they told us it might've.
夢はもう諦めます
I'm already giving up on my dreams.
This cynical mind says "why'd you try?"
"Why not give up and play the bad guy?"
わかってるさ
I know.
運命が波立ちながらあなたを咽び泣こうとするのなら 崩れ落ちそうな体を抱きしめとくから
If fate stirs up waves and tries to make you weep, I'll hold your collapsing body close.
We choose to know
The struggles of this scuffed up age we're living in
the struggles of this scuffed-up age we're living in.
腐ったクソの日々だけど この夜明けは
Despite these rotten, crappy days, this dawn
Could seem a lot like "not your day"
それでも あなたを捨ててしまわないで
but still, don't throw yourself away.
Can't find a reason to stay
Some busted world led astray
in some busted world led astray,
Once trusted, left to decay
We choose to go on anyway.
Lost in thoughts of always changing pace
Allies and friends hiding more than one face
Not really surprising, why are you compromising?
The sun is rising A new horizon
With friendships lacking lies and The knives in your back, so what are you prioritizing?
You aren't sick of crying? See, I don't buy it. But here we are, hanging on, fighting strong despite it.
僅かじゃ表しきれない もう目を閉じてしまいたいぐらいの世間
A world so dim it can barely be expressed, makes me want to close my eyes.
This cynical mind says "why'd you try?" "Why not give up and play the bad guy?"
わからないんだ 埃まみれの街で あなたのため息の影 私の微かな火で 照らしたいだけ
I don't know why, in this dust-covered town, I just want to illuminate your sigh's shadow with my faint fire.
We choose to know The struggles of this scuffed up age, we're giving in 泥土に汚れて
We choose to know the struggles of this scuffed-up age, we're giving in, soiled in mud.
Be real, it hurts to grow
Believing in a world of hate is overrated まあ、でも あなたは美しいのだから
Believing in a world of hate is overrated, but hey, because you are beautiful,
Must be something surreal An endless dream we can't heal
it must be something surreal—an endless dream we can't heal.
This rusted world wound up real Still wanna love the way it feels.
Late nights, the city feels dead, sure, but like... The lights and sights and sounds are treasures.
こんな世界に抗って歩く力なんて私にはないけれど
I don't have the strength to walk defying such a world,
Face up, this world can't kill that inner spark
but face up, this world can't kill that inner spark.
Why don't we turn this Scuffed up page we're writing in こんな世界じゃ
Why don't we turn this scuffed-up page we're writing in? In this kind of world,
Be real, I think we know この夜明けは
be real, I think we know this dawn
Is rarely fair, decide your fate It's your life
あなたを捨ててしまわないで 明日したいだけ
Don't throw yourself away, I just want to bring tomorrow.
We choose to know The struggles of this scuffed up age We're giving in
We choose to know the struggles of this scuffed-up age, we're giving in.
曇った空の下じゃ
Beneath the cloudy skies,
Be real, it hurts to grow
Believing in a world that is overrated My demo あなたは美しいのだから
Believing in a world that is overrated, my demo, because you are beautiful,
Must be something surreal An endless dream we can't heal This rusted world wound up real
Still wanna love the way it feels.
Late nights the city feels that your butt like
Late nights the city feels that, your butt-like...
The lights and sights and sounds are treasures
どんな世界に抗って歩く力なんて私にはないけれど
I don't have the strength to walk defying any world,
Face up, this world can't kill that inner spark
but face up, this world can't kill that inner spark.
Why don't we turn this scuffed up page we're writing in
Why don't we turn this scuffed-up page we're writing in?
So won't know all the way it feels
Way too soon to know
The structure of the scaffold
A page we live in
So don't give in
...and you DEAD BEATS!!
Happy 5 years.
Here's to more.
What are you still doing here?
The show's over!
Go watch the music video!
Thank you Yulis and Nanalysis for the 3D!
Bye!
Thank you all for 5 incredibly
strange, wonderful, whimsical,
at times painful, but so, so special
Years as your Mori.
There are so many more
views I want to see, but
for now, just know how thankful
I am that I get to be your
Pink woman. Always.
We laughed. We cried. We cringed.
And we'll do it again dammit!!
𝓍𝓍𝓍 Calliope Mori